<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
    <markers>
        <marker 
        name="Advantage Phsyiotherapy" 
        lat="51.6665909" 
        lng=" -0.5652450000000044" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="3 Nightingales Corner" 
        address2="Little Chalfont" 
        city="Amersham" 
        state="Buckinghamshire" 
        postal="HP7 9PY" 
        country="UK"
        phone="01494 764 822"
        email="enquiries@advantage-physiotherapy.co.uk" 
        details="sw12694.smart-web.dk/advantage-phsyiotherapy/"
        web="www.advantage-physiotherapy.co.uk" 
        hours1="opening hours include weekdays, late evenings and weekends" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
chronic pain management,
clinical pilates (one to one),
electro-acupuncture,
ergonomics,
exercise classes,
gait analysis,
home visits,
hypermobility,
interferential and therapeutic ultrasound,
knee clinic,
low back pain,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
musculo-skeletal services,
musculoskeletal ultrasound,
neck pain,
pilates,
post natal physio,
post surgery physiotherapy,
postural correction,
rehabilitation services,
remedial massage,
running clinic,
sports massage,
vestibular physiotherapy,
whiplash,
womens health physiotherapy,
yoga" 
        practiceImage="AdvantagePhsyiotherapy.gif"
        practiceDescription="At Advantage Physiotherapy Ltd, we aim to treat you better and help you stay that way. We treat a variety of conditions including back, neck and joint pains, sports injuries, soft tissue injuries, osteoarthritis and much more. We use a combination of treatment techniques varying from acupuncture, ultrasound, exercises, traction and Pilates to hands on treatment such as massage, mobilisation and manipulation. We also have specialist physios in women's health and paediatrics."
       
       clinicianImage1=""
        clinicianName1=""
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Allen Physiotherapy Rehabilitation and Sports Medicine" 
        lat="51.24119169999999" 
        lng="-0.5759510999999975" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="60 Woodbridge Road"
        address2="" 
        city="Guildford" 
        state="Surrey" 
        postal="GU1 4RF" 
        country="UK"
        phone="01483 571783"
        email="admin@physiosportsmed.co.uk/reception@physiosportsmed.co.uk"
        details="sw12694.smart-web.dk/allen-physiotherapy-rehabilitation-and-sports-medicine/"
        web="www.physiosportsmed.co.uk/" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="clinical pilates (one to one),
hydrotherapy,
isokinetic testing,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
musculoskeletal ultrasound,
neck pain,
physiotherapy,
pilates,
rehabilitation services,
remedial massage,
sports massage"
practiceImage="AllenPhysiotherapyRehabilitationandSportsMedicine/allenfront.jpg"
practiceDescription="Allen Physiotherapy, Rehabilitation and Sports Medicine was established in Guildford in 1979 under the name Matthews Allen Physiotherapy. Our main clinic is situated in the heart of Guildford with convenient road and rail links. We also have a physiotherapy clinic in London Battersea, should this be more convenient for you."        
clinicianImage1="AllenPhysiotherapyRehabilitationandSportsMedicine/johnallen.jpg"
        clinicianName1="John Allen - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1="John started the first Sports Council injury clinic at Crystal Palace National Sports Centre, and subsequently three British Olympic Association accredited clinics. Lecturer and clinical tutor, post-graduate doctors, MSc in Sports Medicine, London University. Clinical tutor and examiner, Physiotherapy MSc, Sports Rehabilitation BSc, London Universities. Doctorate in musculoskeletal screening; incorporating implementation of musculo-skeletal assessment for elite UK Athletes. Senior Clinical Fellow Hertfordshire University. Fellow of the Royal College of Medicine Coaching education to senior coaching level in all track and field events including coaching to achieve athletes Olympic selection. Lead physiotherapist, GB, Olympic and England Athletics, including the 2010 Commonwealth Games in Delhi. Expert witness for physiotherapy medico-legal reporting. John has always been a keen sportsman and was a junior international hurdler; later playing league volleyball and competing in triathlon."
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2="Dan Nicholls - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio2="Dan is a qualified Pilates instructor with Body Control Pilates, and has a keen interest in strength and conditioning. In addition to working at the clinic Dan conducts one-to-one sessions at the clinic’s hydrotherapy pool."
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3="Lucy Eggleton - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio3="Lucy has completed an MSc in Physiotherapy and has a BSc (Hons) in Sports Rehabilitation and Injury Prevention. She has an interest in Hypermobility (being extra flexible) and has traveled internationally with Track and Field Athletics works across both our Guildford and Battersea Sites providing Physiotherapy and Sports Massage services and she also runs our Hydrotherapy sessions in Guildford."
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4="Stuart Butler - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio4="Stuart has a background in Strength and Conditioning and has a keen interest in biomechanics and their application in the treatment and prevention of Injuries."
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Back2normal" 
        lat="51.50249239999999" 
        lng="-0.07357579999995778" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="44 Curlew Street"
        address2="Butlers Wharf" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="SE1 2ND" 
        country="UK"
        phone="02073576877"
        email="info@back2normal.co.uk" 
        details="sw12694.smart-web.dk/back2normal/"
        web="www.back2normal.co.uk" 
        hours1="8am-6pm Monday-Friday" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="electro-acupuncture,
exercise classes,
gym,
interferential and therapeutic ultrasound,
low back pain,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
neck pain,
physiotherapy,
post surgery physiotherapy,
rehabilitation services,
sports medicine,
whiplash" 
        practiceImage=""
        practiceDescription=""
        clinicianImage1=""
        clinicianName1=""
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
          <marker 
        name="Backworks" 
        lat="51.5402074" 
        lng="0.7064388000000008" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="96 London Road"
        address2="" 
        city="Southend-on-Sea" 
        state="Essex" 
        postal="SS1 1PG" 
        country="UK"
        phone="01702 342329"
        email="backworkssouthend@gmail.com"
        details="sw12694.smart-web.dk/backworks/" 
        web="www.backpainsouthend.com" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="chiropractic,
physiotherapy" 
        practiceImage="Backworks/Backworksdesk.jpg"
        practiceDescription="With a special interest in chronic mechanical/degenerative low back pain, the Backworks team has been serving Essex since 1996. We have developed a close working relationship with consultants and GP’s. We are proud to be the exclusive chiropractors for Southend United Football and Southend Rugby Football clubs. Our practitioners are registered with AXA/PPP, BUPA, WPA and most major healthcare providers."
        clinicianImage1="Backworks/Backworks.JPG"
        clinicianName1="Lester Brayham - Registered Chiropractor 00531"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Balance Performance Physiotherapy" 
        lat="51.4650743" 
        lng="-0.13091989999998077" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="113 Gauden Road"
        address2="Clapham" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="SW4 6LE" 
        country="UK"
        phone="020 7627 2308"
        email="admin@balancephysio.com"
        details="sw12694.smart-web.dk/balance-performance-physiotherapy/" 
        web="www.balancephysio.com" 
        hours1="Mon, Tues, Wed, Thursday 6.00am until 9.00pm. Friday 6.00am until 6.00pm Saturday 8.00am until 5.00pm Open Bank Holiday Mondays and Good Friday. Closed Boxing Day, Xmas Day and New Year's Day" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
chronic pain management,
clinical pilates (one to one),
ergonomics,
exercise classes,
gait analysis,
gym,
home visits,
hypermobility,
injection therapy,
interferential and therapeutic ultrasound,
knee clinic,
low back pain,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
musculo-skeletal services,
musculoskeletal ultrasound,
neck pain,
neurophysiotherapy,
nutritional therapy,
osteopathy,
osteoporosis physiotherapy,
personal training,
physiotherapy,
pilates,
podiatry,
post natal physio,
post surgery physiotherapy,
postural correction,
rehabilitation services,
remedial massage,
running clinic,
sports massage,
sports medicine,
whiplash,
women's health,
womens health physiotherapy" 
        practiceImage=""
        practiceDescription="The largest rehabilitation space in London dedicated to the treatment, rehabilitation and performance enhancement of all sports men and women, incorporating dedicated and specialist areas for back and neck injuries, post surgical rehabilitation and reconstruction, performance analysis studio for runners and cyclists, gym, studio, and Pilates and ergonomic suites. Currently we have 35 of the most professional professionals who all work together for your good."
        clinicianImage1=""
        clinicianName1=""
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        

        <marker 
        name="Barbican Physiotherapy Clinic" 
        lat="51.51829550000001" 
        lng=" -0.09318749999999909" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="1 The Postern"
        address2="Wood Street" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="EC2Y 8BJ" 
        country="UK"
        phone="020 7606 6530 / 020 7628 4182"
        email="info@barbicanphysio.co.uk" 
        details="sw12694.smart-web.dk/barbican-physiotherapy-clinic"
        web="www.barbicanphysio.co.uk" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
gait analysis,
pilates"
        practiceImage="BarbicanPhysiotherapyClinic/BarbicanPhysiotherapyCliniclogo2.bmp"
        practiceDescription="Barbican Physiotherapy Clinic has been operating since 1980 and as always, we aim to be the number one choice for physiotherapy in the City. As well as accepting consultant, GP and self referrals, our practice also provides a service to many leading city companies including: JP Morgan, Cazenove Capital, Dechert LLP, Slaughter and May, Clifford Chance and Linklaters. We are recognised by all the major health insurers including Bupa and Axa PPP with whom we have a long standing successful relationship. We are proud of our reputation within the city and this success is down to maintaining extremely high levels of patient care provided by our team of exceptionally experienced physiotherapists, all with significant post graduate or Masters level qualifications. We aim to provide a comprehensive treatment plan with a mainly hands-on approach encompassing traditional manual therapy techniques as well as acupuncture and pilates style rehabilitation. Additional services such at gait/running assessments and orthotic prescription can also be accessed. Our goal is to return our patients to full levels of fitness and function, ensuring they leave with an on-going rehabilitation plan and a knowledge that allows them to self manage their condition with the support of their physiotherapist and in close liaison with their consultant." 
        clinicianImage1="BarbicanPhysiotherapyClinic/ChrisPicture2.JPG"
        clinicianName1="Christine O’Flaherty - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2="BarbicanPhysiotherapyClinic/EmilyStri.JPG"
        clinicianName2="Emily Strickland - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio2="Graduated from King’s College London in 1998, working at Guy’s and St Thomas’ hospitals for the next five years gaining invaluable physiotherapy and medical experience. In 2007 she completed a Masters in Sports physiotherapy from Cardiff University whilst working with the British Army. In this job she was physiotherapist to the British Army cricket team as well as treating and rehabilitating a variety of training injuries and multiple trauma injuries of serving soldiers. She specialises in all fields of musculoskeletal physiotherapy but especially sporting conditions and injuries involving the lower limb. She also has experience in women’s health, assisting with pregnancy related musculoskeletal complaints as well as post natal returning to exercise, including pelvic floor training. She enjoys the challenge of complex rehabilitation and returning people back to activity both at professional and recreational levels. As an adjunct to treatment, she utilises acupuncture, core stability training and biomechanical assessment with orthotic prescription where appropriate."
        clinicianImage3="BarbicanPhysiotherapyClinic/NickGrim.JPG"
        clinicianName3="Nick Grimwood - Physiotherapist
"
        clinicianBio3="Qualified from St Marys Hospital, Paddington in 1993 then spent 7 years working for the NHS at University College London Hospital before spending a year providing physiotherapy for the Saudi Royal family in Rhyad and Casablanca. On his return, he joined a Harley Street Practice for 12 years giving treatment to patients with spinal injuries and people needing post-surgical rehabilitation. After gaining his Masters in sports rehabilitation, he worked for the Great British Judo team and Blackheath Rugby club. Nick prides himself on his analytical ‘problem-solving approach to physiotherapy. Along with treating the problem at hand with manual therapy, he will also search for the causes to the problem and will provide advice, movement correction and exercises to prevent re-occurance. This is especially useful with recurring spinal or sports injuries."
        clinicianImage4="BarbicanPhysiotherapyClinic/Murtagh.JPG"
        clinicianName4="Peter Murtagh - Physiotherapist
"
        clinicianBio4="Qualified as a physiotherapist in 2001 from the University of Hertfordshire and has latterly gone on to do an MSc in advanced physiotherapy at Kings College London as well as qualifying to be a MACP member (an association for physiotherapists that have reached standards of excellence). He has worked as a senior physiotherapist within the NHS for 6 years and in the private sector for over 4 years as well as with Arsenal football club. Peter has extensive experience in dealing with neck and back pain, sports injuries, muscle imbalance problems, stiff and painful joints, rehabilitation post surgery and long standing chronic painful conditions. Peter uses an array of treatment techniques and has excellent manual therapy skills as well as being qualified to do acupuncture. Peter has both a very holistic and analytical approach to understanding and treating the client’s presenting problem. As well as directly treating the current symptoms Peter always aims to identify the causal factors underlying the problem and therefore prevent re injury. He also regards informing the patient as fully as possible re their condition as an essential element of treatment."
        clinicianImage5="BarbicanPhysiotherapyClinic/SimonHoward.JPG"
        clinicianName5="Simon Howard - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio5="Graduated from the University of East London in 1997. He gained invaluable experience during four years at the Royal Free Hospital and is now the longest serving physiotherapist at this clinic having been based here since summer 2002. He played semi-professional basketball at Crystal Palace which enhances his special interest in sports injuries and musculo-skeletal rehabilitation. He practices manual therapy and core stability training for spinal dysfunction and also uses acupuncture as an occasional ancillary treatment. He like the others undertakes many post graduate courses which underpin his skills in clinical practice."
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Battersea Physio" 
        lat="51.4649136" 
        lng="-0.1792164999999386" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="Battersea Sports Centre"
        address2="Hope Street" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="SW11 2DA" 
        country="UK"
        phone="0208 685 6930"
        email="info@surreyphysio.co.uk"
        details="sw12694.smart-web.dk/battersea-physio/" 
        web="www.batterseaphysio.co.uk" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
            chronic pain management,
            clinical pilates (one to one),
            ergonomics,
            gait analysis,
            gym,
            home visits,
            interferential and therapeutic ultrasound,
            knee clinic,
            low back pain,
            musculoskeletal diagnostic ultrasound,
            musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
            musculo-skeletal services,
            musculoskeletal ultrasound,
            neck pain,
            physiotherapy,
            post natal physio,
            post surgery physiotherapy,
            postural correction,
            rehabilitation services,
            running clinic,
            sports massage,
            whiplash,
            women's health,
            womens health physiotherapy" 
        practiceImage=""
        practiceDescription="Battersea Physio is one of the leading physiotherapy clinics in the Battersea, Wandsworth and Clapham areas, with a reputation of attracting clients from far. They have a team of well trained, friendly clinicians who have a keen interest in sport and who have worked with many top athletes including Olympic athletes. They treat a wide range of sports and non sports related injuries and are highly recommended in the area as an affordable and professional clinic."
        clinicianImage1=""
        clinicianName1=""
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
      

        <marker 
        name="Beyond Health" 
        lat="51.4758656" 
        lng="-0.20095790000004854" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="Swan Mews"
        address2="Parsons Green" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="
SW6 4QT" 
        country="UK"
        phone="0207 610 7070"
        email="be@beyond-health.co.uk"
        details="" 
        web="www.beyond-health.co.uk" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="osteopathy,
personal training,
physiotherapy,
sports massage" 
        practiceImage="BeyondHealth/BeyondHealthImage.jpg"
        practiceDescription="Beyondhealth is a contemporary sports physiotherapy, sports injury and back pain clinic. Situated a short stroll from Parsons Green tube down the cobbled Swan Mews. Fulham Physiotherapy. Fulham’s favourite Physio’s have set up this unique partnership simply so you can be offerred the best possible care. We have 8 physios on staff"
        clinicianImage1="BeyondHealth/BeyondHealthTeam.JPG"
        clinicianName1="Mark Bender - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Bodies Under Construction Chiswick" 
        lat="51.4746447" 
        lng="-0.25525089999996453" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="The Riverside Health and Racquets Club"
        address2="Dukes Meadows" 
        city="Chiswick" 
        state="Greater London" 
        postal="W4 2SX" 
        country="UK"
        phone="02087474029"
        email="Info@bodiesunderconstruction.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.bodiesunderconstruction.com" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
hydrotherapy,
musculo-skeletal services,
osteoporosis physiotherapy,
physiotherapy,
pilates,
rehabilitation services,
sports medicine,
women's health"
        practiceImage=""
        practiceDescription="We have one simple philosophy. We help you feel well, and teach you strategies to maintain that wellness! As a multidisciplinary practice we deliver a range of complementary wellness therapies in addition to our main Physiotherapy and Pilates services including acupuncture, sports massage, myofascial release, hypnotherapy, personal training and nutritional consultations. We deal with people from all walks of life, from the sedentary office worker to the elite athlete. We have the expertise to help you reach your peak performance. Our experienced Physiotherapists can treat all musculoskeletal problems including spinal and sports injuries. We can tailor a treatment programme that will use a combination of manual therapy, dry needling/acupuncture and exercise therapy including Clinical Pilates. In addition to our Physiotherapy treatment rooms, we have access to world-class facilities at The Riverside Club(just over Barnes Bridge) including the hydrotherapy pool and gymnasium. We have our own fully equipped Pilates Studio offering Private and Duet Pilates sessions, we also have a full class timetable of Pilates equipment classes for rehabilitation, functional re-education and fitness. These sessions are conducted by both Physiotherapists and highly qualified Pilates Instructors." 
 clinicianImage1="BodiesUnderConstructionChiswick/1Ellen.JPG"
        clinicianName1="Ellen Ernstzen - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1=""
     clinicianImage2="BodiesUnderConstructionChiswick/2Jo.JPG"
        clinicianName2="Jo Coulter - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio2=""
 clinicianImage3="BodiesUnderConstructionChiswick/3Leslie.JPG"
        clinicianName3="Leslie Abrahams - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio3=""
 clinicianImage4="BodiesUnderConstructionChiswick/4Luke.JPG"
        clinicianName4="Luke Headley - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio4=""
 clinicianImage5="BodiesUnderConstructionChiswick/5Rebecca.JPG"
        clinicianName5="Rebecca Harris - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
     
     
        <marker 
        name="Bodies Under Construction Putney" 
        lat="51.46165939999999" 
        lng="-0.2199442999999519" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="The Putney Clinic of Physical Therapy"
        address2="2nd Floor, 266 Upper Richmond Road" 
        city="Putney" 
        state="Greater London" 
        postal="SW15 6TQ" 
        country="UK"
        phone="0208 789 3881"
        email="Info@bodiesunderconstruction.com"
        details="" 
        web="www.bodiesunderconstruction.com" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
hydrotherapy,
musculoskeletal diagnostic ultrasound,
osteoporosis physiotherapy,
physiotherapy,
pilates,
post surgery physiotherapy,
sports medicine,
women's health" 
        practiceImage=""
        practiceDescription="We have one simple philosophy. We help you feel well, and teach you strategies to maintain that wellness! As a multidisciplinary practice we deliver a range of complementary wellness therapies in addition to our main Physiotherapy and Pilates services including acupuncture, sports massage, myofascial release, hypnotherapy, personal training and nutritional consultations. We deal with people from all walks of life, from the sedentary office worker to the elite athlete. We have the expertise to help you reach your peak performance. Our experienced Physiotherapists can treat all musculoskeletal problems including spinal and sports injuries. We can tailor a treatment programme that will use a combination of manual therapy, dry needling/acupuncture and exercise therapy including Clinical Pilates. We have partnered with the Putney Clinic of Physical Therapy. In addition to our Physiotherapy treatment rooms, we also have our own fully equipped Pilates studio. We offer Private and Duet Exercise sessions for rehabilitation, functional re-education as well as fitness. These sessions are conducted by both Physiotherapists and Pilates Instructors. The Putney Clinic is part of London's largest NHS and Private Medical Treatment Facility We provide a complete cycle of care; from the immediate treatment of your pain and injury rehabilitation through to lifestyle changes and preventative exercise for your complete body and mind wellbeing."
    clinicianImage1="BodiesUnderConstructionPutney/1Bhav.JPG"
        clinicianName1="Bhavini Mistry - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1=""
    clinicianImage2="BodiesUnderConstructionPutney/2David.JPG"
        clinicianName2="David Richmond - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio2=""
    clinicianImage3="BodiesUnderConstructionPutney/3Katie.JPG"
        clinicianName3="Katie Howard - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio3=""
    clinicianImage4="BodiesUnderConstructionPutney/4Leslie.JPG"
        clinicianName4="Leslie Abrahams - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        

            <marker 
        name="Bodybalance Physiotherapy &amp; Sports Injury Clinic" 
        lat="51.76078099999999" 
        lng="-0.25006600000006074" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="Hertfordshire Sports Village"
        address2="de Havilland Campus" 
        city="Hatfield" 
        state="Hertfordshire" 
        postal="AL10 9EU" 
        country="UK"
        phone="01707284910"
        email="info@bodybalancephysio.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.bodybalancephysio.com" 
        hours1="MONDAY - THURSDAY: 8 am - 8 pm FRIDAY: 8 am - 6pm SATURDAY: 8 am - 1 pm" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
        clinical pilates (one to one),
        exercise classes,
        gait analysis,
        gym,
        home visits,
        hydrotherapy,
        hypermobility,
        knee clinic,
        low back pain,
        musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
        musculo-skeletal services,
        neck pain,
        physiotherapy,
        pilates,
        post surgery physiotherapy,
        rehabilitation services,
        remedial massage,
        running clinic,
        sports massage,
        whiplash" 
        practiceImage="BodybalancePhysiotherapySportsInjuryClinic/Hatfield/MainImage.jpg"
        practiceDescription="Bodybalance Physiotherapy &amp; Sports Injury Clinic offer physiotherapy, massage, and clinical Pilates in Hertfordshire and North London. Specialists in sports injuries, our team of highly skilled and experienced clinicians understand your needs and have the knowledge to help you manage your injury, reduce your pain and return you to your optimal level of activity. But we don’t just treat sports injuries – we can help you with all kinds of injuries including back pain, neck pain, muscle strains, ligament sprains and tendon pains; and we’re great with post-op rehabilitation. Through our holistic approach we will tailor our treatments to your individual goals and specific requirements, working with you to optimise your recovery and prevent recurrence."
clinicianImage1="BodybalancePhysiotherapySportsInjuryClinic/Hatfield/EricClarke.JPG"
        clinicianName1="Eric Clarke – Director, Sports Physiotherapist."
        clinicianBio1="B App Sc (Physio) M (Sports Physio). Australian Sports Physiotherapist with 15 years’ experience. Specialises in hip, knee and ankle injuries. Elite sailing experience with Artemis Racing in 34th Americas Cup and the Australian Olympic Team at 2008 Beijing Olympics"
        clinicianImage2="BodybalancePhysiotherapySportsInjuryClinic/Hatfield/CliniciansImage.jpg"
        clinicianName2="Bodybalance Physiotherapy &amp; Sports Injury Clinic"
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>

        
    
        <marker 
        name="Bodybalance Physiotherapy &amp; Sports Injury Clinic" 
        lat="51.59995809999999" 
        lng="-0.23573869999995622" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="Laboratory Spa &amp; Health Club"
        address2="1a Hall Lane" 
        city="Hendon" 
        state="London" 
        postal="NW4 4TJ" 
        country="UK"
        phone="01707284910"
        email="info@bodybalancephysio.com"
        details="" 
        web="www.bodybalancephysio.com" 
        hours1="MONDAY - THURSDAY: 8 am - 8 pm FRIDAY: 8 am - 6 pm SATURDAY: 9 am - 1 pm" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
clinical pilates (one to one),
gym,
home visits,
hydrotherapy,
hypermobility,
knee clinic,
low back pain,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
musculo-skeletal services,
neck pain,
physiotherapy,
pilates,
post surgery physiotherapy,
rehabilitation services,
remedial massage,
running clinic,
sports massage,
sports medicine,
whiplash" 
        practiceImage="BodybalancePhysiotherapySportsInjuryClinic/Hendon/MainImage1.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="Bodybalance Physiotherapy and Sports Injury Clinic offer physiotherapy, massage, and clinical Pilates in Hertfordshire and North London. Specialists in sports injuries, our team of highly skilled and experienced clinicians understand your needs and have the knowledge to help you manage your injury, reduce your pain and return you to your optimal level of activity. But we don’t just treat sports injuries – we can help you with all kinds of injuries including back pain, neck pain, muscle strains, ligament sprains and tendon pains; and we’re great with post-op rehabilitation. Through our holistic approach we will tailor our treatments to your individual goals and specific requirements, working with you to optimise your recovery and prevent recurrence."
        clinicianImage1=""
        clinicianName1=""
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Broadgate Spine and Joint Clinic" 
        lat="51.5168354" 
        lng="-0.08651740000004793" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="65 London Wall"
        address2="" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="EC2M 5TU" 
        country="UK"
        phone="02076384330"
        email="Chris@movementperfected.com"
        details="" 
        web="www.broadgatespinecentre.co.uk" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
physiotherapy,
pilates" 
    practiceImage="BroadgateSpineAndJointClinic/MainImage1.bmp" 
        practiceDescription="Musculoskeletal Physiotherapist with additional qualifications in Rehabilitative Pilates (Machine and Mat based), MACP Grade V Manipulation and Acupuncture qualified. Building up a vast portfolio of treatment methods, I believe the key to rehabilitation is in the detail. Integrating the very latest in evidence based practice to treatment and exercise plans. Most importantly making sure that they dovetail with my client lifestyles."
    clinicianImage1="BroadgateSpineAndJointClinic/Andre1.png"
        clinicianName1="Andre Bason - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1="Specialising in physiotherapy"
clinicianImage2="BroadgateSpineAndJointClinic/MainImage2.jpg"
        clinicianName2="Broadgate Spine and Joint Clinic"
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Central Health Physiotherapy" 
        lat="51.5174423" 
        lng="-0.1129280000000108" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="Chancery House"
        address2="53-64 Chancery Lane" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="WC2A 1QS" 
        country="UK"
        phone="020 7404 6343"
        email="reception@central-health.com"
        details="" 
        web="www.central-health.com" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="ergonomics,
neurophysiotherapy,
osteoporosis physiotherapy,
physiotherapy,
vestibular physiotherapy" 
    practiceImage="CentralHealthPhysiotherapy/MainImage1.bmp" 
        practiceDescription="Central Health Physiotherapy's aim is to return, maintain and build your health and fitness. We operate out of seven clinics across London: Chancery Lane, the Hospital of St John &amp; St Elizabeth in St John’s Wood, the Royal Hospital Chelsea (with hydrotherapy pool), Farringdon, Notting Hill, Roehampton and Barnet (with hydrotherapy pool)."
clinicianImage1="CentralHealthPhysiotherapy/1Christopher.JPG"
        clinicianName1="Christopher Pinches - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2="CentralHealthPhysiotherapy/2Gemma.jpg"
        clinicianName2="Gemma Newell - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio2=""
    clinicianImage3="CentralHealthPhysiotherapy/3Hayley.JPG"
        clinicianName3="Hayley Dalton - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio3=""
    clinicianImage4="CentralHealthPhysiotherapy/4Natasha.jpg"
        clinicianName4="Natasha Price - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio4="MD and Owner of CHP"
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Central Health Physiotherapy - Hospital of St John and St Elizabeth" 
        lat="51.5333227" 
        lng="-0.17504170000006525" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="The Hospital of St John and St Elizabeth"
        address2="60 Grove End Road" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="NW8 9NH" 
        country="UK"
        phone="020 7806 4010"
        email="physiotherapy@hje.org.uk"
        details="" 
        web="www.thephysiotherapyunit.org.uk" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="ergonomics,
hypermobility,
neurophysiotherapy,
physiotherapy,
vestibular physiotherapy,
womens health physiotherapy" 
    practiceImage="CentralHealthPhysiotherapy/MainImage1.bmp" 
        practiceDescription="The Physiotherapy Unit at the Hospital of St John and St Elizabeth is one of the UK's leading physio centres, offering a comprehensive range of services at your convenience. Our department is staffed by experienced chartered physiotherapists whose variety of specialist skills and interests cover every area. They work closely with some of country's finest consultants and nurses, offering the highest standard of specialist care and attention."
clinicianImage1="CentralHealthPhysiotherapy/1Christopher.JPG"
        clinicianName1="Christopher Pinches - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1=""
    clinicianImage2="CentralHealthPhysiotherapy/4Natasha.jpg"
        clinicianName2="Natasha Price - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio2="MD and Owner of CHP"
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="City Road Physio" 
        lat="51.5274369" 
        lng="-0.08910820000005515" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="First Floor - Kemp House"
        address2="152-160 City Road" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="EC1V 2NP" 
        country=""
        phone="0207 608 8500"
        email="info@cityroadphysio.co.uk"
        details="" 
        web="www.cityroadphysio.co.uk" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="physiotherapy" 
        practiceImage="CityRoadPhysio/MainImage1.png" 
        practiceDescription="At City Road Physio, we passionately believe that every patient is an individual. We aim to provide not only top quality manipulative and exercise therapy, but also ensure that we tailor our intervention to the specific needs and aims of the patient. We have a strong record in all areas of spinal care, whether your aims are just to get through the working day without pain, or to run the next London marathon. We have gym facilities and individual treatment rooms at city road, so that we can provide all that you will require to get better."
        clinicianImage1=""
        clinicianName1="Susan Julians - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Covent Garden Physiotherapy and Sports Injury Clinic" 
        lat="51.5109900" 
        lng="-0.1242640" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="Ground Floor, 23-24"
        address2="Henrietta Street" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="WC2E 8ND" 
        country="UK"
        phone="0207 497 8974"
        email="info@coventgardenphysio.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.coventgardenphysio.com" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="gym
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
pilates,
rehabilitation services,
women's health" 
practiceImage="CoventGardenPhysiotherapyAndSportsInjuryClinic/MainImage1.png" 
        practiceDescription="Covent Garden Physiotherapy was established in 1990. Our aim is to offer high quality physiotherapy from well qualified clinicians. Our philosophy is to listen to the individual needs of the patient whilst delivering evidence based treatment. We believe that the relationship between the physiotherapist and the patient is important and the same physiotherapist will deliver the treatment from 'hands on' to end stage rehabilitation. Whether your goal is to walk unaided without a limp or train for an ultra marathon; we will help you to achieve your personal goal. With exercise and advice we aim to keep the treatments to a minimum."
        clinicianImage1="CoventGardenPhysiotherapyAndSportsInjuryClinic/ClinicianImage1.JPG"
        clinicianName1="Team"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2="Anthony Vidis - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio2="Anthony has experience in treating and rehabilitating sports and spinal injuries and has a special interest in both knee and shoulder pathologies."
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3="Emma McCabe - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio3="Specialising in: home visits, physiotherapy, pilates. Emma is a qualified Clinical Pilates instructor, which she teaches on a one to one basis, carefully selecting specific exercises depending on the condition. She uses Pilates and general exercise to rehabilitate all conditions, which includes exercises on the Pilates reformer. Emma is available for early and evening appointments or can also visit your home for convenience"
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4="Harriet Hodgskin - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio4="Harriet‘s clinical interests include sports injuries, cervicogenic neck pain, postural correction, headaches and the shoulder."
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5="Heather Grant - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio5="Heather has special interests in manipulative therapy having completed a further three year part time course to become a member of the manipulation association of chartered physiotherapists."
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6="Kevin Kong - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio6="Specialising in: physiotherapy, rehabilitation services. Kevin has experience in treating and rehabilitating spinal injuries and sports injuries and he integrates his gym and exercise knowledge into his rehabilitation programmes. He came to London in 2003 and joined our team in October 2007."
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7="Mark Edmonds - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio7="Specialising in: physiotherapy, remedial massage. Mark has a special interest in runners, triathletes offering sports specific massage and advice. He is well qualified to offer this as he is an ex-triathlete for the GB team. Massage to relieve work related upper back, neck and shoulder tension."
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8="Nora Mulcahy - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio8="Being a keen sports person, Nora was drawn towards sports related injuries. She has worked with a number of sports teams including Rugby, Australian Rules and Football."/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Cranfold Physical Therapy Centre" 
        lat=" 51.1416740" 
        lng="-0.4899010" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="107 High Street"
        address2="" 
        city="Cranleigh" 
        state="Surrey" 
        postal="GU6 8AU" 
        country="UK"
        phone="	01483 267747"
        email="reception@cranfoldphysio.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="www.cranfoldphysio.co.uk" 
        hours1="Monday 08.30-19.00 Tuesday 08.30-21.00 Wednesday 08.30-19.00 Thursday 08.30-20.00 Friday 09.00-17.00 Saturday 09.00-13.00" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
clinical pilates (one to one),
ergonomics,
home visits,
interferential and therapeutic ultrasound,
low back pain,
musculoskeletal diagnostic ultrasound,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
musculo-skeletal services,
neck pain,
physiotherapy,
pilates,
podiatry,
post surgery physiotherapy,
remedial massage,
sports massage,
sports medicine" 

practiceImage="CranfoldPhysicalTherapyCentre/CranleighPracticeImage.JPG" 
        practiceDescription="Cranfold Physical Therapy Centre was established in 1999 and offers a wide range of therapies across our sites in Surrey and Sussex. We are able to offer appointments within 48 hours, with a wide range of times to suit everyone, including late evenings and Saturday morning appointments in Cranleigh ."
clinicianImage1="CranfoldPhysicalTherapyCentre/MainImage1.jpg"
        clinicianName1="Cranfold Physical Therapy Centre"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Cranfold Physical Therapy Centre" 
        lat="51.2352380" 
        lng="-0.3248320" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="The Medwyn Centre"
        address2="Reigate Road" 
        city="Dorking" 
        state="Surrey" 
        postal="RH4 1SD" 
        country="UK"
        phone="01306 740784"
        email="reception@cranfoldphysio.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="www.cranfoldphysio.co.uk" 
        hours1="Monday 09.00-17.30 Tuesday 09.00-17.30 Wednesday 08.30-13.30 Thursday 09.00-17.30 Friday 08.30-17.30" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
home visits,
interferential and therapeutic ultrasound,
low back pain,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
neck pain,
physiotherapy,
post surgery physiotherapy" 
        practiceImage="CranfoldPhysicalTherapyCentre/DorkingPracticeImage.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="Cranfold Physical Therapy Centre was established in 1999 and offers a wide range of therapies across our sites in Surrey and Sussex. We are able to offer appointments within 48 hours, with a wide range of times to suit everyone, including late evenings and Saturday morning appointments in Cranleigh."
clinicianImage1="CranfoldPhysicalTherapyCentre/MainImage1.jpg"
        clinicianName1="Cranfold Physical Therapy Centre"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Cranfold Physical Therapy Centre" 
        lat="51.0607300" 
        lng="-0.3270700" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="Total Therapy Studios"
        address2="2 Denne Parade" 
        city="Horsham" 
        state="West Sussex" 
        postal="RH12 1JD" 
        country="UK"
        phone="0845 025 4000"
        email="reception@cranfoldphysio.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="www.cranfoldphysio.co.uk" 
        hours1="Monday 09.30-20.00 Tuesday 09.30-14.30 Wednesday 12.30-20.00 Thursday 17.00-20.00 Friday - From Jan 2015 Saturday - From Jan 2015" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
home visits,
interferential and therapeutic ultrasound,
low back pain,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
neck pain,
physiotherapy,
post surgery physiotherapy" 
practiceImage="CranfoldPhysicalTherapyCentre/HorshamPracticeImage.jpg" 
practiceDescription="Cranfold Physical Therapy Centre was established in 1999 and offers a wide range of therapies across our sites in Surrey and Sussex. We are able to offer appointments within 48 hours, with a wide range of times to suit everyone, including late evenings and Saturday morning appointments."
clinicianImage1="CranfoldPhysicalTherapyCentre/MainImage1.jpg"
        clinicianName1="Cranfold Physical Therapy Centre"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>

        <marker 
        name="Cranfold Physical Therapy Centre" 
        lat="51.0237180" 
        lng="-0.3503610" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="The Village Surgery"
        address2="Station Road" 
        city="Southwater" 
        state="West Sussex" 
        postal="RH13 9HQ" 
        country="UK"
        phone="0845 025 4000"
        email="reception@cranfoldphysio.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="www.cranfoldphysio.co.uk" 
        hours1="Monday 14.00-18.00 Wednesday - 09.30-11.30 (Pilates classes only) Thursday 08.30-13.00" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
clinical pilates (one to one),
home visits,
interferential and therapeutic ultrasound,
low back pain,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
neck pain,
physiotherapy,
pilates,
post surgery physiotherapy" 
practiceImage="CranfoldPhysicalTherapyCentre/SouthwaterPracticeImage.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="Cranfold Physical Therapy Centre was established in 1999 and offers a wide range of therapies across our sites in Surrey and Sussex. We are able to offer appointments within 48 hours, with a wide range of times to suit everyone, including late evenings and Saturday morning appointments in Cranleigh."
clinicianImage1="CranfoldPhysicalTherapyCentre/MainImage1.jpg"
        clinicianName1="Cranfold Physical Therapy Centre"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Croydon Physio" 
        lat="51.3552970" 
        lng="-0.0441610" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="Addington Palace"
        address2="Gravel Hill" 
        city="Croydon" 
        state="Surrey" 
        postal="CR0 5BB" 
        country="UK"
        phone="0208 662 5059"
        email="info@croydonphysio.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="croydonphysio.co.uk" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
chronic pain management,
clinical pilates (one to one),
ergonomics,
gait analysis,
gym,
home visits,
injection therapy,
knee clinic,
low back pain,
musculoskeletal diagnostic ultrasound,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
musculo-skeletal services,
musculoskeletal ultrasound,
neck pain,
neurophysiotherapy,
osteopathy,
osteoporosis physiotherapy,
physiotherapy,
pilates,
post natal physio,
post surgery physiotherapy,
postural correction,
rehabilitation services,
remedial massage,
sports massage,
sports medicine,
vestibular physiotherapy,
whiplash,
women's health,
womens health physiotherapy" 
        practiceImage="CroydonPhysio/MainImage1.JPG" 
        practiceDescription="Croydon Physiotherapy Clinic is the leading provider of physiotherapy in Croydon. They have a team of well trained, friendly clinicians who have a keen interest in sport. Their expertise ranges from treatment of the elderly, children, pregnant women, and sports injuries. Croydon Physio are also able to offer Osteopathy and Clinical Pilates."
        clinicianImage1=""
        clinicianName1=""
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Darren Chandler" 
        lat="51.5293410" 
        lng="-0.0316510" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="98a Coborn Road"
        address2="Bow" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="E2DG" 
        country="UK"
        phone="02089809664"
        email="darren@spineplusbow.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="www.spineplus.co.uk" 
        hours1="9am - 8pm" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture, 
                  clinical pilates (one to one),
                  osteopathy" 
        practiceImage="DarrenChandler/MainImage1.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="Osteopath Specialising in chronic spinal pain, disc pathology etc."
        clinicianImage1="DarrenChandler/ClinicianImage1.jpg"
        clinicianName1="Darren Chandler B.Ost.Med, (Hons) D.O"
        clinicianBio1="Occupational Therapist, specialising in osteopathy. Darren is a director and co founder of Spine Plus Clinics, and the Harley Street Spine Clinic. He is a full member of the British Osteopathic Association (BOA), British Medical Acupuncture Society (BMAS) and is a state-registered osteopath with the General Osteopathic Council (GOsC). Darren qualified as an osteopath after a five-year degree course, and was presented with the 2002 Student of the Year Award by HRH Princess Anne. His patients now include some of the country’s leading dancers and sportsmen. Darren specialises in the diagnosis and treatment of spinal, sports and work-related injuries. He has a particular passion for identifying spinal conditions that have been missed by other medical practitioners, and now receives referrals for patients with undiagnosed conditions from GPs and pain consultants across the capital. Darren provides clinical assessments for patients self-referring for MRI scans at one of London’s leading diagnostic centres, Vista Diagnostics. He also holds back-pain tutorials for GPs and gives talks to medical audiences on spinal injuries. To expand his medical knowledge, Darren regularly shadows orthopaedic surgeons, pain consultants and musculoskeletal radiologists. In 2008, he established The National Back Pain Helpline with Spine Plus colleague Robert Shanks. The service functions as a source of information and guidance for people with low back pain, neck pain, sciatic pain (sciatica) and other spine-related disorders. www.nationalbackpainhelpline.co.uk. Darren, a self-confessed perfectionist, played badminton at a national level as a teenager and was one of the country’s leading pianists in his age group. He is now dedicated to osteopathy and expanding his knowledge of spinal injuries. Darren explains: 'Back pain is a complex issue that is often mismanaged. Its causes and effects vary from one individual to another. Many patients come to me having tried a number of different treatments without success. As part of my work I try to unravel the mystery and complexities surrounding back pain. I use clinical reasoning and evidence-based practice, but also intuition gained from years of practice and research. It's important to remember no two patients (or practitioners) are alike.' Darren has lived in the East End for 36 years. He is married with new arrival Zac. He is a single-handicap golfer and a trained fitness instructor."
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Elaine Atkins Physiotherapy" 
        lat="51.5996590" 
        lng="0.0205910" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="154 High Road"
        address2="Woodford Green" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="IG8 9EF" 
        country="UK"
        phone="020 8504 0478"
        email="management@elaineatkins.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.elaineatkins.com" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="neurophysiotherapy" 
    practiceImage="ElaineAtkinsPhysiotherapy/MainImage1.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="We are a musculoskeletal practice with highly qualified physiotherapists headed by Dr Elaine Atkins who has taught on postgraduate courses with the Society of Musculoskeletal Medicine for over 20 years. All our physiotherapists are experienced in the assessment, clinical diagnosis and treatment of all musculoskeletal problems – notably back and neck pain, joint disorders and soft tissue injuries. We use mobilisations, soft tissue techniques, manipulation and exercises to treat pain, promote healing and to restore function - helped by acupuncture and electrotherapy and always with appropriate education and advice. Our specialist neurophysiotherapist provides an additional service to patients with neurological conditions, including MS, head injury, Parkinson’s disease and stroke. The culture of Elaine Atkins Physiotherapy is based on respect for our patients, referrers, suppliers and staff alike with support, effective communication and a willingness to ‘go the extra mile’ whenever needed."
        clinicianImage1="ElaineAtkinsPhysiotherapy/1Elaine.jpg"
        clinicianName1="Elaine Atkins - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1="Specialising in: neurophysiotherapy, physiotherapy"
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="ESPH (Dulwich)" 
        lat="51.4559920" 
        lng="-0.0765020" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="116 Lordship Lane"
        address2="East Dulwich" 
        city="London" 
        state="Greater London" 
        postal="SE22 8HD" 
        country="UK"
        phone="0208 693 2493"
        email="info@esph.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="www.esph.co.uk" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
dietetics,
ergonomics,
gym,
isokinetic testing,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
physiotherapy,
post natal physio,
sports massage,
yoga" 
        practiceImage="ESPH/MainImage1.bmp" 
        practiceDescription="Our branch in East Dulwich specialises in musculoskeletal injuries, sports injury, overuse injury and post operative rehabilitation. Using the original core principals of quality, expertise and discretion ESPH combines our expertise in physiotherapy consultation and treatment services with a modern fully comprehensive gym facility and state of the art pilates studio. Our patients are all given a free 3 month rehabilitation membership. Our treatment rooms are contemporary and inviting offering patients the opportunity to enjoy home from home style facilities. Treatment is provided by our expert team of handpicked health care professionals led by world renowned physiotherapist Elizabeth Sharp. In 5 years ESPH East Dulwich has established itself as a market leader in South East London, quickly becoming the 1st choice practise for patients and practitioners alike."
        clinicianImage1="ESPH/ClinicImage.JPG"
        clinicianName1="ESPH (Dulwich)"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>

        <marker 
        name="ESPH (Harley Street)" 
        lat="51.5178690" 
        lng="-0.1461180" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="22 Harley Street"
        address2="" 
        city="London" 
        state="Greater London" 
        postal="W1G 9PL" 
        country="UK"
        phone="0207 907 1900"
        email="info@esph.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="www.esph.co.uk" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
ergonomics,
low back pain,
musculoskeletal diagnostic ultrasound,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
neck pain,
pilates,
podiatry" 
        practiceImage="ESPH/MainImage1.bmp" 
        practiceDescription="Specialising in the treatment of musculoskeletal conditions, our world renowned Harley Street practise has been offering leading physiotherapy and rehab services for over three decades. Adopting ESPH core principals of quality, expertise and discretion, Esph is the first choice practise for insurance companies, individuals and professionals in health care. Our prestigious Central London practise offers efficient and comprehensive treatment in musculoskeletal injuries, sports injuries, overuse injuries and post operative rehabilitation. With sworn testimonials and strong anecdotal evidence to show that our fusion of modern and traditional methods are proven to work and make a significant difference to the lives and wellbeing of our patients."
        clinicianImage1="ESPH/ClinicImage1.JPG"
        clinicianName1="ESPH (Harley Street)"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="First Physio" 
        lat="51.5915990" 
        lng="0.0320970" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="5 Ashford Road"
        address2="South Woodford" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="E18 1JZ" 
        country="UK"
        phone="0208 989 6848"
        email="admin@first-physio.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="www.first-physio.co.uk" 
        hours1="Monday – Friday 9am – 7pm Saturday 9am – 1pm" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
physiotherapy,
sports massage," 
        practiceImage="FirstPhysio/MainImage.gif" 
        practiceDescription="Corner property building, 4 treatment rooms, 3 receptionists, Disabled toilet, sink in each room. electric treatment plinths pay and display parking. 3 minutes from underground station."
        clinicianImage1="FirstPhysio/1Nicola.png"
        clinicianName1="Nicola Vineyard - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2="FirstPhysio/2Ruth.png"
        clinicianName2="Ruth Cohen - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Garry Trainer Clinic" 
        lat="51.5401040" 
        lng="-0.1512330" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="65 Princess Road"
        address2="Primrose Hill" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="NW1 8JS" 
        country="UK"
        phone="020 7722 6203"
        email="garry@garrytrainer.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.garrytrainer.com" 
        hours1="Mon / Tues - 7am-8pm" 
        hours2="Weds/Thurs - 8am-7pm" 
        hours3="Fri - 7am-7pm, Sat - 9am-6pm, Sun - 9am-1pm" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
low back pain,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
musculo-skeletal services,
neck pain,
osteopathy,
physiotherapy,
post natal physio,
postural correction,
rehabilitation services,
remedial massage,
sports massage" 
        practiceImage="GarryTrainerClinic/MainImage1.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="The centre of excellence in London offering osteopathy, acupuncture, physiotherapy and massage,Garry Trainer Clinic specialises in bringing you relief from pain and restoring your mobility. Based in Primrose Hill, North West London, we have 30 years of experience specialising in Back, Neck, Shoulder and Joint Pain, Sports Injuries and Rehabilitation, Sciatica, Upper and Lower Limb Disorders, Functional Rehabilitation, Migraines, Stress and Anxiety, Pre and Post Pregnancy Management"
        clinicianImage1=""
        clinicianName1=""
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Harley Street Physiotherapy" 
        lat="51.5212670" 
        lng="-0.1493550" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="12 Upper Wimpole Street"
        address2="" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="W1G 6LW" 
        country="UK"
        phone="020 7224 4588"
        email="harleystphysio@btconnect.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.harleystreetphysiotherapy.co.uk" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="physiotherapy" 
    practiceImage="HarleyStreetPhysiotherapy/MainImage1.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="Harley Street Physiotherapy was established in 1987 by Antiopdeans Pippa Warrell and Elisabeth Buchanan. Having worked closely with respected consultants and doctors in the unique Harley Street area for over 20 years, we have a deep understanding of patient needs across a very broad range of musculoskeletal problems, enabling us to provide the highest standard of physiotherapy. We pride ourselves on our quality and depth of our patient care."
    clinicianImage1="HarleyStreetPhysiotherapy/MainImage2.jpg"
        clinicianName1="Harley Street Physiotherapy"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="In Motion Physiotherapy Ltd." 
        lat="51.5171040" 
        lng="-0.1728800" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="Winston Churchill Building, St Mary's Hospital"
        address2="Praed St" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="W2 1NY" 
        country="UK"
        phone="07582444601"
        email="imphysio1@gmail.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.imphysiotherapy.com" 
        hours1="Clinic hours: 17.45 - 21.00 Home visits weekdays and weekends on request" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
chronic pain management,
clinical pilates (one to one),
ergonomics,
gait analysis,
gym,
home visits,
hydrotherapy,
knee clinic,
low back pain,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
musculo-skeletal services,
musculoskeletal ultrasound,
neck pain,
osteoporosis physiotherapy,
personal training,
physiotherapy,
pilates,
post natal physio,
post surgery physiotherapy,
postural correction,
rehabilitation services,
sports massage,
sports medicine,
vestibular physiotherapy,
whiplash,
women's health,
womens health physiotherapy" 
        practiceImage="InMotionPhysiotherapyLtd/MainImage1.png" 
        practiceDescription="In Motion Physiotherapy is a private physiotherapy practice, which offers a wide variety of services. The expert clinicians in the team deliver high levels of Musculo-Skeletal Physiotherapy, Women’s health Physiotherapy, Vestibular rehabilitation, Hydrotherapy, Acupuncture and Deep Tissue Massage. Our team offers individually tailored assessment and rehabilitation programs. At In Motion Physiotherapy, we believe in giving you back the power and confidence to manage your problem in the long term. We are covered by most health insurance companies."
        clinicianImage1=""
        clinicianName1=""
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
       
        <marker 
        name="Josephine Lawson Physiotherapy Clinic" 
        lat="51.5125970" 
        lng="-0.0792430" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="107 Fenchurch Street"
        address2="" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="EC3M 5JF" 
        country="UK"
        phone="020 7488 4924"
        email="care@cityphysio.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="www.cityphysio.co.uk" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="physiotherapy" 
practiceImage="JosephineLawsonPhysiotherapyClinic/MainImage1.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="We have three clinics between London Bridge and Bank. Our main Clinic has a small gym with running machine and cycle , from where we can assess gait, advise on cycling techniques and give specific exercise programmes. We have podiatry, chiropody, specialist Pilates teacher, sports massage therapy and women’s health physio.We see a variety of musculo skeletal problems from sporting injuries to back and neck problems brought on by long periods of poor sitting posture. We pride ourselves in getting our patients back to work and play quickly!"
clinicianImage1="JosephineLawsonPhysiotherapyClinic/1Chris.jpg"
        clinicianName1="Chris Brookes - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1=""
clinicianImage2="JosephineLawsonPhysiotherapyClinic/2Josephine.jpg"
        clinicianName2="Josephine Lawson - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio2=""
clinicianImage3="JosephineLawsonPhysiotherapyClinic/3Louise.jpg"
        clinicianName3="Louise Mann - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio3=""
clinicianImage4="JosephineLawsonPhysiotherapyClinic/4Sam.jpg"
        clinicianName4="Sam Fielder - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio4=""
clinicianImage5="JosephineLawsonPhysiotherapyClinic/5Tosin.jpg"
        clinicianName5="Tosin Eyitaya - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Kensington Physio and Sports Medicine" 
        lat="51.5141320" 
        lng="-0.1998870" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="Notting Hill"
        address2="11 Lambton Place" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="W11 2SH" 
        country="UK"
        phone="020 3553 2190"
        email="info@kenphysio.com" 
        details=""
        web="http://www.kenphysio.com/about/locations/notting-hill-lambton-place/" 
        hours1="Monday: 8:00 am – 8:00 pm " 
        hours2="Tuesday: 8:00 am – 8:00 pm" 
        hours3="Wednesday: 8:00 am – 8:00 pm Thursday: 8:00 am – 8:00 pm Friday: 8:00 am – 5:00 pm" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
chronic pain management,
clinical pilates (one to one),
ergonomics,
exercise classes,
gait analysis,
gym,
home visits,
low back pain,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
musculo-skeletal services,
neck pain,
nutritional therapy,
personal training,
physiotherapy,
pilates,
post surgery physiotherapy,
postural correction,
rehabilitation services,
remedial massage,
running clinic,
sports massage,
sports medicine,
whiplash" 
practiceImage="KensingtonPhysioandSportsMedicine/MainImage1.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="Kensington Physiotherapy and Sports Medicine practice are proud to be working with The Spine Surgery London team. We specialise in the management of spinal pain including neck and low back symptoms. Treatment and management of acute, persistent, surgical and complex presentations. Comprehensive rehabilitation to allow return to normal function, work or high level sport."
        clinicianImage1=""
        clinicianName1=""
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Kensington Physio and Sports Medicine" 
        lat="51.4941310" 
        lng="-0.1683330" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="Chelsea at The Westover"
        address2="13 Crescent Place" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="SW3 2EA" 
        country="UK"
        phone="0207 603 0040"
        email="" 
        details=""
        web="http://www.kenphysio.com/about/locations/chelsea-crescent-place/" 
        hours1="Monday: 8:00 am – 8:00 pm Tuesday: 8:00 am – 8:00 pm Wednesday: 8:00 am – 8:00 pm Thursday: 8:00 am – 8:00 pm Friday: 8:00 am – 5:00 pm" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
chronic pain management,
clinical pilates (one to one),
ergonomics,
exercise classes,
gait analysis,
gym,
home visits,
knee clinic,
low back pain,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
musculo-skeletal services,
musculoskeletal ultrasound,
neck pain,
nutritional therapy,
personal training,
physiotherapy,
pilates,
post natal physio,
post surgery physiotherapy,
postural correction,
rehabilitation services,
running clinic,
sports massage,
sports medicine,
whiplash,
women's health,
womens health physiotherapy" 
practiceImage="KensingtonPhysioandSportsMedicine/MainImage1.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="Kensington Physiotherapy and Sports Medicine practice are proud to be working with The Spine Surgery London team. We specialise in the management of spinal pain including neck and low back symptoms. Treatment and management of acute, persistent, surgical and complex presentations. Comprehensive rehabilitation to allow return to normal function, work or high level sport."
        clinicianImage1=""
        clinicianName1=""
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Kensington Physio and Sports Medicine" 
        lat="51.5000270" 
        lng="-0.2112120" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="7 Russell Gardens"
        address2="Kensington" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="W14 8EZ" 
        country="UK"
        phone="0207 603 0040"
        email="info@kenphysio.com" 
        details=""
        web="" 
        hours1="8am - 8pm Monday to Friday" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
chronic pain management,
clinical pilates (one to one),
ergonomics,
exercise classes,
gait analysis,
gym,
home visits,
knee clinic,
low back pain,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
musculo-skeletal services,
neck pain,
physiotherapy,
post natal physio,
post surgery physiotherapy,
postural correction,
rehabilitation services,
remedial massage,
running clinic,
sports massage,
sports medicine,
whiplash,
women's health,
womens health physiotherapy" 
practiceImage="KensingtonPhysioandSportsMedicine/MainImage2.JPG" 
        practiceDescription="Kensington Physiotherapy and Sports Medicine practice are proud to be working with The Spine Surgery London team. We specialise in the management of spinal pain including neck and low back symptoms. Treatment and management of acute, persistent, surgical and complex presentations. Comprehensive rehabilitation to allow return to normal function, work or high level sport."
clinicianImage1="KensingtonPhysioandSportsMedicine/1David.jpg"
        clinicianName1="David O'Neil - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1="Specialising in: 
acupuncture, chronic pain management, ergonomics, exercise classes, gait analysis, gym, home visits, knee clinic, low back pain, musculo-skeletal physiotherapy, musculo-skeletal services, musculoskeletal ultrasound, neck pain, physiotherapy, post surgery physiotherapy, postural correction, rehabilitation services, running clinic, sports massage, sports medicine, whiplash.David is Clinical Lead at Kensington Physio &amp; Sports Medicine Practice and has a wealth of experience in the treatment of acute, persistent and complex spinal conditions including both low back and neck related symptoms. His interest in this area took him out to Perth Australia in 2008 to study a Masters at Curtin University in the management of spinal pain"
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
       
        <marker 
        name="Kensington Physio and Sports Medicine" 
        lat="51.5000270" 
        lng="-0.2112120" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="Wandsworth at The Westover"
        address2="15 Bellevue Road" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="SW17 7EG" 
        country="UK"
        phone="0207 603 0040"
        email="info@kenphysio.com" 
        details=""
    web="http://www.kenphysio.com/about/locations/wandsworth-bellevue-road/" 
        hours1="Monday: 8:00 am – 8:00 pm Tuesday: 8:00 am – 8:00 pm Wednesday: 8:00 am – 8:00 pm Thursday: 8:00 am – 8:00 pm Friday: 8:00 am – 5:00 pm" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
chronic pain management,
clinical pilates (one to one),
ergonomics,
exercise classes,
gait analysis,
home visits,
knee clinic,
low back pain,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
musculo-skeletal services,
musculoskeletal ultrasound,
neck pain,
nutritional therapy,
personal training,
physiotherapy,
pilates,
postural correction,
rehabilitation services,
remedial massage,
running clinic,
sports massage,
sports medicine,
whiplash,
women's health,
womens health physiotherapy" 
practiceImage="KensingtonPhysioandSportsMedicine/MainImage1.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="Kensington Physiotherapy and Sports Medicine practice are proud to be working with The Spine Surgery London team. We specialise in the management of spinal pain including neck and low back symptoms. Treatment and management of acute, persistent, surgical and complex presentations. Comprehensive rehabilitation to allow return to normal function, work or high level sport."
        clinicianImage1=""
        clinicianName1=""
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>

        <marker 
        name="Marylebone Physiotherapy and Sport Medicine" 
        lat="51.5233860" 
        lng="-0.1601840" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="Health Consultants Inc."
        address2="8 Dorset Square" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="NW1 6PU" 
        country="UK"
        phone="0845 370 8222"
        email="info@marylebonephysio.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.marylebonephysio.com" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
dance medicine,
home visits,
musculoskeletal ultrasound,
physiotherapy,
pilates,
running clinic" 
practiceImage="MarylebonePhysiotherapyandSportMedicine/MainImage1.gif" 
        practiceDescription="Marylebone Physiotherapy &amp; Sports Medicine is a clinic that specialises in musculoskeletal, orthopaedic, spinal and sports medicine rehabilitation. The team strives to be innovative and proactive in their approach to treatment and every patient is treated as an individual. There is a real sense of excitement and positive momentum in the clinic. Chris McLean is constantly pushing the boundaries of what the clinic delivers and developing his unique style of physiotherapy aimed at optimising human performance. The clinic has developed an international reputation in the treatment of complex musculoskeletal disorders and success with these patients is testament to the ongoing development and evolution of treatment approaches within the clinic. Continuous professional development is a key element to the clinic’s success and the team work very closely together and with referring consultants to ensure each patient achieves their individual goals. Patients should expect an exceptional experience where they can be guided through the stages of their treatment in a positive, efficient and enjoyable manner."
clinicianImage1="MarylebonePhysiotherapyandSportMedicine/1Amy.JPG"
        clinicianName1="Amy Glasgow - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1=""
clinicianImage2="MarylebonePhysiotherapyandSportMedicine/2Chris.JPG"
        clinicianName2="Chris Mclean - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio2=""
clinicianImage3="MarylebonePhysiotherapyandSportMedicine/3SimonGilchrist.JPG"
        clinicianName3="Simon Gilchrist - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Oxford Circus Physiotherapy" 
        lat="51.5173164" 
        lng="-0.1418540" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="Oxford Circus Physio"
        address2="33 Great Titchfield Street" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="W1W 7PA" 
        country="UK"
        phone="02076365774"
        email="reception@oxfordcircusphysio.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="www.oxfordcircusphysio.co.uk" 
        hours1="Mon: Thurs 8.00am - 19.00pm Fri: 8.00am - 18.00pm" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
chronic pain management,
clinical pilates (one to one),
gait analysis,
interferential and therapeutic ultrasound,
knee clinic,
low back pain,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
musculoskeletal ultrasound,
neck pain,
personal training,
physiotherapy,
pilates,
podiatry,
post natal physio,
post surgery physiotherapy,
rehabilitation services,
remedial massage,
sports massage,
womens health physiotherapy" 
    practiceImage="OxfordCircusPhysiotherapy/MainImage1.png" 
        practiceDescription="Oxford Circus Physio is home to expert Physiotherapy, Sports and Remedial Massage clinicians and High Performance coaches providing leading edge Rehabilitation and Sports Performance right in the heart of London’s West End. We have over 12 years experience including being part of Olympic and Commonwealth games, professional sporting franchises and various educational programmes. The facilities are brand new and purpose built to meet all rehabilitation needs – there are full gym facilities with an indoor 20m Sprint track."
    clinicianImage1=""
        clinicianName1=""
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Physio on the River Ltd" 
        lat="51.4727350" 
        lng="-0.2521500" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="The Old Ticket Office,
                 Barnes Bridge, The Terrace"
        address2="Barnes" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="SW13 0NP" 
        country="UK"
        phone="020 8876 5690"
        email="help@physio-on-the-river.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="www.physio-on-the-river.co.uk" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
chronic pain management,
home visits,
physiotherapy,
pilates,
yoga" 
        practiceImage="PhysioOnTheRiverLtd/MainImage1.bmp" 
        practiceDescription="Diana Wilson established Physio on the River 20 years ago in 1993. It has grown from a small Physiotherapy clinic into a much larger multidisciplinary practice specialising in the treatment of everyday aches and pains and injury management. Our clinic is friendly and welcoming and we put great store on nurturing our clients and tailoring our treatments to the individual. All our clinicians are highly qualified and experienced and most have worked here for many years. Last year we were awarded the ‘most loved Physiotherapy clinic’ in the Borough of Richmond upon Thames. Although still primarily a Physiotherapy clinic we also provide services which complement Physiotherapy in the treatment of spinal conditions: most of our physiotherapists are also trained in acupuncture for pain relief, our massage therapists can help relieve muscular tension, our specialist Ergonomics Physiotherapist can visit your home or work office and carry out a work station assessment for work related aches and pains and we run a programme of Pilates and yoga classes and individual sessions to help promote core strength which is so important in the treatment of back and neck conditions. Our aim is to help you recover from injury or surgery and then help you to maintain that good health through regular safe exercise."
        clinicianImage1="PhysioOnTheRiverLtd/1DianaWilson.jpg"
        clinicianName1="Diana Wilson - Director"
        clinicianBio1="Physiotherapist"
        clinicianImage2="PhysioOnTheRiverLtd/2HelenaLawson.JPG"
        clinicianName2="Helena Lawson - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio2=""
    clinicianImage3="PhysioOnTheRiverLtd/3LeanneAntoine.JPG"
        clinicianName3="Leanne Antoine - Lead Clinician"
        clinicianBio3="Physiotherapist"
        clinicianImage4="PhysioOnTheRiverLtd/4RichardGame.JPG"
        clinicianName4="Richard Game - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5="PhysioOnTheRiverLtd/5SophieCannon.JPG"
        clinicianName5="Sophie Cannon - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Physio Solutions" 
        lat="51.5331090" 
        lng="-0.1094020" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="23 Baron Street"
        address2="" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="N1 9ET" 
        country="UK"
        phone="020 7713 7780"
        email="info@physiosolutions.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="www.physiosolutions.co.uk" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="clinical pilates (one to one),
ergonomics,
physiotherapy,
sports massage" 
        practiceImage="PhysioSolutions/MainImage1.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="Physio Solutions is a team of specialist musculo-skeletal clinicians based near the Angel in Islington and we also have a satellite Clinic near Highbury. All of our physiotherapists have post-graduate qualifications an and a minimum of seven years post-graduate experience. We are recognised by all the private insurance companies."
        clinicianImage1="PhysioSolutions/1DanielBrown.jpg"
        clinicianName1="Daniel Brown - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2="PhysioSolutions/2HelenSkehan.jpg"
        clinicianName2="Helen Skehan - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3="PhysioSolutions/3JadePattison.jpg"
        clinicianName3="Jade Pattison - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="PhysioQinetics (Staines)" 
        lat="" 
        lng="" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="Spelthorne Leisure Centre"
        address2="Knowle Green" 
        city="Staines-upon-Thames" 
        state="Surrey" 
        postal="TW18 1AJ" 
        country="UK"
        phone="01784 532388"
        email="michelle.lai@physioqinetics.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.physioQinetics.com" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="chronic pain management,
electro-acupuncture,
interferential and therapeutic ultrasound,
physiotherapy" 
        practiceImage="PhysioQinetics/MainImage1.bmp" 
        practiceDescription="We are a friendly physiotherapy clinic with specialist knowledge and skills in the treatment of musculoskeletal conditions. We believe in a manual treatment approach and that there is no substitute for experienced 'hands-on' techniques to provide effective, first-class, professional therapy to our patients."
        clinicianImage1="PhysioQinetics/1MichelleLai.jpg"
        clinicianName1="Michelle Lai - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>

        <marker 
        name="PhysioQinetics (Uxbridge)" 
        lat="" 
        lng="" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="198 Harlington Road"
        address2="" 
        city="Uxbridge" 
        state="Greater London" 
        postal="UB8 3HA" 
        country="UK"
        phone="01895 255139"
        email="michelle.lai@physioqinetics.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.physioQinetics.com" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="chronic pain management,
electro-acupuncture,
interferential and therapeutic ultrasound,
physiotherapy" 
        practiceImage="PhysioQinetics/MainImage1.bmp" 
        practiceDescription="We are a friendly physiotherapy clinic with specialist knowledge and skills in the treatment of musculoskeletal conditions. We believe in a manual treatment approach and that there is no substitute for experienced 'hands-on' techniques to provide effective, first-class, professional therapy to our patients."
        clinicianImage1="PhysioQinetics/1MichelleLai.jpg"
        clinicianName1="Michelle Lai - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Physiotherapy @ 30, Devonshire Street" 
        lat="" 
        lng="" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="30, Devonshire Street"
        address2="Marylebone" 
        city="London" 
        state="Greater London" 
        postal="W1G 6PU" 
        country="UK"
        phone="02079083660"
        email="" 
        details=""
        web="http://theprincessgracehospital.com/hospital-services/services/physiotherapy/#Outpatient" 
        hours1="08:00 to 18:00 Monday to Friday" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
chronic pain management,
clinical pilates (one to one),
ergonomics,
exercise classes,
gait analysis,
gym,
hydrotherapy,
hypermobility,
interferential and therapeutic ultrasound,
knee clinic,
low back pain,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
musculo-skeletal services,
musculoskeletal ultrasound,
neck pain,
physiotherapy,
pilates,
post surgery physiotherapy,
postural correction,
rehabilitation services,
running clinic,
sports medicine,
whiplash" 
        practiceImage="" 
        practiceDescription="Physiotherapy is treatment by physical means. The profession uses a range of such treatment types to reduce pain and increase function. Assessment, diagnosis, problem identification and appropriate treatments are determined by sound clinical reasoning and are at the core of our physiotherapists' skills. All physiotherapists employed at 30, Devonshire Street are specialists in the outpatient management of orthopaedic and musculoskeletal conditions including sports injuries. The initial assessment is the most important component of your care. It includes a detailed history of the problem and a specific physical examination based on the history. After the assessment the physiotherapist will explain the findings of the assessment and discuss the treatment plan with the patient. Our clinic can assist in the treatment and management of: Post-operative rehabilitation; post fracture management; back and neck pain; headaches; sports injuries; work related injuries; general joint and soft tissue dysfunction; management of complaints after breast cancer treatment. Treatment types used at 30, Devonshire Street: Exercise therapy; manual therapy including manipulation; movement analysis and retraining; acupucture; hydrotherapy. Other services include pilates and hand therapy. All of our team are HCPC registered, members of the Acupuncture Association of Physiotherapists and the Chartered Society of Physiotherapy. They all have gained considerable experience in treating musculoskeletal injuries and have completed extensive post-graduate academic training. The department also runs weekly in-service training to allow our staff to keep their skills and knowledge honed."
        clinicianImage1=""
        clinicianName1=""
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Physiotherapy in Chelsea" 
        lat="51.4943016" 
        lng="-0.1597830" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="47 Cadogan Square"
        address2="Chelsea" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="SW3 2QJ" 
        country="UK"
        phone="020 7584 9054"
        email="mail@physio-chelsea.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="www.physio-chelsea.co.uk" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="physiotherapy,
postural correction" 
        practiceImage="PhysiotherapyinChelsea/MainImage1.gif" 
        practiceDescription="A caring and motivational approach: A very high focus on detailed assessment, leading to precise treatment. Once pain is settled, a careful guided programme to full strength and activities."
        clinicianImage1="PhysiotherapyinChelsea/1Uth.png"
        clinicianName1="Carsten Uth - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>

<marker 
        name="Physit" 
        lat="51.4644110" 
        lng="-0.2679120" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="First Floor"
        address2="182 Upper Richmond Road West" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="SW14 8AW" 
        country="UK"
        phone="07714 244438"
        email="info@physit.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="www.physit.co.uk" 
        hours1="Monday - Friday 07.30 - 20.30 Saturday 07.30 - 13.00" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
chiropractic,
clinical pilates (one to one),
electro-acupuncture,
ergonomics,
exercise classes,
gait analysis,
home visits,
interferential and therapeutic ultrasound,
low back pain,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
musculo-skeletal services,
musculoskeletal ultrasound,
neck pain,
neurophysiotherapy,
nutritional therapy,
osteoporosis physiotherapy,
physiotherapy,
pilates,
post natal physio,
post surgery physiotherapy,
rehabilitation services,
running clinic,
sports massage,
whiplash,
womens health physiotherapy" 
        practiceImage="Physit/MainImage1.png" 
        practiceDescription="At Physit our physiotherapist will provide you with a full assessment, treatment and rehabilitation programme of exercises specific to your individual needs and monitor you on your road to recovery. A thorough assessment from our physio will help you understand the extent of your injury to enable the best possible healing outcomes. We use a variety of techniques to optimize healing for your injury. These include “hands-on” for the treatment of your pain and spasm. Some patients also require taping to enable better mechanical facilitation of muscles for performance or in the case of patellofemoral pain treatment such as massage, joint mobilization and manipulation. There may also be a need for elecrotherapy agents such as ultrasound and interferential. We may also use acupuncture."
        clinicianImage1="Physit/1Phoebe.jpg"
        clinicianName1="Phoebe Machin - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1="Phoebe graduated with a Bachelor of Science (Physiotherapy) from Sydney University in 1995. She has over 15 years of experience of physiotherapy practice. Prior to this degree Phoebe gained an Associate Diploma of Health Science (Sport and Exercise) at New England University which has given her a focus in the sports injury field of physiotherapy practice. Phoebe’s special interests include: - Spinal injuries – disc, nerve pain, spinal rehabilitation following surgery - Sports/Acute injuries – tennis elbow, ACL and ligament injuries of the knee - Headaches/Migraines - Palliative Care – use of acupuncture - Adolescent growth plate injuries – Osgood Schlatter’s, Sever’s disease "
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Physit" 
        lat="51.4724250" 
        lng="-0.2010960" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="Way of Therapy"
        address2="257 New Kings Road" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="SW6 4RB" 
        country="UK"
        phone="07714 244438"
        email="info@physit.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="www.physit.co.uk" 
        hours1="Wednesday 16.00- 20.00" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
clinical pilates (one to one),
electro-acupuncture,
ergonomics,
exercise classes,
gait analysis,
home visits,
interferential and therapeutic ultrasound,
low back pain,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
musculo-skeletal services,
musculoskeletal ultrasound,
neck pain,
neurophysiotherapy,
osteoporosis physiotherapy,
physiotherapy,
pilates,
post natal physio,
post surgery physiotherapy,
rehabilitation services,
running clinic,
sports massage,
whiplash,
women's health,
womens health physiotherapy" 
        practiceImage="Physit/MainImage1.png" 
        practiceDescription="At Physit our physiotherapist will provide you with a full assessment, treatment and rehabilitation programme of exercises specific to your individual needs and monitor you on your road to recovery. A thorough assessment from our physio will help you understand the extent of your injury to enable the best possible healing outcomes. We use a variety of techniques to optimize healing for your injury. These include “hands-on” for the treatment of your pain and spasm. Some patients also require taping to enable better mechanical facilitation of muscles for performance or in the case of patellofemoral pain treatment such as massage, joint mobilization and manipulation. There may also be a need for elecrotherapy agents such as ultrasound and interferential. We may also use acupuncture."
        clinicianImage1="Physit/1Dylan.jpg"
        clinicianName1="Dylan Woodhead BSc (Exercise Science) MSc (Rehabilitation Science) MCSP HCPC Registered Consultant Physiotherapist - Occupational Therapist"
        clinicianBio1="Dylan studied Master of Science in Physiotherapy at the University of Brighton. Dylan's special interests include: - Sport Injuries - Complex post-cervical spine surgery - Thoracic spine mobility programme - Lumbar spine rehabilitation programme - Core stability education and introduction - Shoulder rehabilitation "
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Prime Health &amp; Fitness" 
        lat="51.3421070" 
        lng="-0.4635230" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="No 10 and 11, Horizon Business Village"
        address2="1 Brooklands Road" 
        city="Weybridge" 
        state="Surrey" 
        postal="KT13 0TJ" 
        country="UK"
        phone="01932 504999"
        email="enquiries@prime-health.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="http://www.prime-health.co.uk" 
        hours1="Monday - Friday 8am - 8pm" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
chronic pain management,
clinical pilates (one to one),
dance medicine,
dietetics,
exercise classes,
gait analysis,
gym,
hypermobility,
injection therapy,
interferential and therapeutic ultrasound,
knee clinic,
low back pain,
musculoskeletal diagnostic ultrasound,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
musculo-skeletal services,
musculoskeletal ultrasound,
neck pain,
neurophysiotherapy,
nutritional therapy,
osteopathy,
personal training,
physiotherapy,
pilates,
podiatry,
post natal physio,
post surgery physiotherapy,
postural correction,
rehabilitation services,
remedial massage,
running clinic,
sports massage,
sports medicine,
vestibular physiotherapy,
whiplash" 
        practiceImage="PrimeHealthandFitness/MainImage1.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="We have one of Surrey's finest Therapy Services with a highly experienced team of Physiotherapists, Osteopaths, Podiatrists, Sports Masseurs, Clinical Pilates Instructors, Strength and Conditioning Coaches working out of 8 beautifully appointed Consulting Rooms and a fully equipped 2000sqft gymnasium to optimise rehabilitation and conditioning"
        clinicianImage1=""
        clinicianName1=""
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Ruislip Physiotherapy Sports and Spinal Clinic" 
        lat="51.5693120" 
        lng="-0.4226610" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="15 West End Road"
        address2="Ruislip" 
        city="Middx" 
        state="Greater London" 
        postal="HA4 6JE" 
        country="UK"
        phone="01895 638 841"
        email="thephysio@ruislipphysio.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.ruislipphysio.com" 
        hours1="opening hours include weekdays, late evenings and weekends" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
chronic pain management,
clinical pilates (one to one),
electro-acupuncture,
ergonomics,
exercise classes,
gait analysis,
home visits,
hypermobility,
interferential and therapeutic ultrasound,
knee clinic,
low back pain,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
musculo-skeletal services,
musculoskeletal ultrasound,
neck pain,
physiotherapy,
pilates,
post natal physio,
post surgery physiotherapy,
postural correction,
rehabilitation services,
remedial massage,
running clinic,
sports massage,
vestibular physiotherapy,
whiplash,
womens health physiotherapy,
yoga" 
        practiceImage="RuislipPhysiotherapySportsandSpinalClinic/MainImage1.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="At Ruislip Physiotherapy, we aim to treat you better and help you stay that way. We treat a variety of conditions including back, neck and joint pains, sports injuries, soft tissue injuries, osteoarthritis and much more. We use a combination of treatment techniques varying from acupuncture, ultrasound, exercises, traction and Pilates to hands on treatment such as massage, mobilisation and manipulation. We also have specialist physios in women's health and paediatrics."
        clinicianImage1=""
        clinicianName1=""
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Scorpio Clinics" 
        lat="51.4055080" 
        lng="-0.5761950" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="Christchurch Road"
        address2="Virginia Water" 
        city="" 
        state="Surrey" 
        postal="GU25 4PX" 
        country="UK"
        phone="01344 845801"
        email="Info@scorpiophysio.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.scorpioclinics.com" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="physiotherapy
pilates" 
        practiceImage="ScorpioClinics/MainImage1.png" 
        practiceDescription="Practice has been operating for over 20 years. We are all highly experienced and inventive manual therapists: but we also place high emphasis on guided rehabilitation exercises. We use both acupuncture and dry needling, mobilisation and manipulation, Sarah Key method, Graston Technique etc We strongly espouse a team approach and work together to ensure each patient gets the best and most appropriate treatment. We have 7 physio + an osteopath. Also 3 pilates instructors and an acupuncturist"
        clinicianImage1="ScorpioClinics/1KarlDewsbury.JPG"
        clinicianName1="Karl Dewsbury - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2="ScorpioClinics/2SophieDhenin.jpg"
        clinicianName2="Sophie Dhenin - Occupational Therapist"
        clinicianBio2="Specialising in: physiotherapy"
        clinicianImage3="ScorpioClinics/3SteveOtt.JPG"
        clinicianName3="Steve Ott - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Sevenoaks Physiotherapy" 
        lat="51.2738460" 
        lng="0.1926580" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="Manor Clinic"
        address2="165 High Street" 
        city="Sevenoaks" 
        state="Kent" 
        postal="TN13 1XJ" 
        country="UK"
        phone="01732 464400"
        email="info@sevenoaksphysiotherapy.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="www.sevenoaksphysiotherapy.co.uk" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="physiotherapy
pilates" 
        practiceImage="SevenoaksPhysiotherapy/MainImage1.bmp" 
        practiceDescription="The clinic is a busy multi-disciplinary practice with physiotherapists working alongside osteopaths, in conjunction with podiatry and sports massage. Our belief is in full rehabilitation be it using our gym and pilates equipment, and integrating patients into self-management attending Pilates and Yoga classes."
        clinicianImage1="SevenoaksPhysiotherapy/1CarolynSearby.jpeg"
        clinicianName1="Carolyn Searby - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1="Although I am a senior clinician we have back specialist physiotherapists Jackie Taylor, Sue Kortum, Helen Boucher and clinical pilates specialist Louise Huntley and Claire Butler-Henderson. Our Osteopath is Sian Eaton"
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Sheen Physiotherapy &amp; Sports Injuries Clinic" 
        lat="51.4638660" 
        lng="-0.2668680" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="151 Sheen Lane"
        address2="East Sheen" 
        city="London" 
        state="Greater London" 
        postal="SW14 8LR" 
        country="UK"
        phone="0208 392 9264"
        email="info@sheenphysiotherapy.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.sheenphysiotherapy.com" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
physiotherapy,
rehabilitation services" 
        practiceImage="SheenPhysiotherapyandSportsInjuriesClinic/MainImage1.JPG" 
        practiceDescription="Our highly qualified and experienced team offer an expert physiotherapy service in a relaxed and welcoming environment. We treat all musculo skeletal injuries including sports related injuries. Our focus is on long term solutions and the prevention of future injuries whilst recognising the need for our clients to return to their daily activities and sports as soon as possible. We also provide rehabilitation physiotherapy following surgery."
        clinicianImage1="SheenPhysiotherapyandSportsInjuriesClinic/1mikeedgar.JPG"
        clinicianName1="Mark Edgar - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2="SheenPhysiotherapyandSportsInjuriesClinic/2stephanieaiken.JPG"
        clinicianName2="Stephanie Aickin - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        
        <marker 
        name="Six Physio (Fleet Street)" 
        lat="51.5138030" 
        lng="-0.1073220" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="36 Whitefriars Street"
        address2="" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="EC4Y 8BQ" 
        country="UK"
        phone="020 7248 6666"
        email="fleet@sixphysio.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.sixphysio.com" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="physiotherapy" 
        practiceImage="SixPhysio/MainImage1.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="Our philosophy at Six Physio is ‘two heads are better than one’. The teamwork between specialist rehab and manual therapist is seamless. We will get to the cause of the problem and show you dynamic, tried and tested rehab strategies. Over 42&#37; of patients who come to us with back pain have failed elsewhere to manage their pain."
        clinicianImage1="SixPhysio/1Alex.JPG"
        clinicianName1="Alex Keogh - Clinic Director"
        clinicianBio1="Physiotherapist"
        clinicianImage2="SixPhysio/2Nichola.JPG"
        clinicianName2="Nichola Roberts - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Six Physio (Fulham)" 
        lat="51.4792540" 
        lng="-0.1944970" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="39 Harwood Road"
        address2="" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="SW6 4QP" 
        country="UK"
        phone="020 7736 0193"
        email="Fulham@sixphysio.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.sixphysio.com" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="physiotherapy" 
        practiceImage="SixPhysio/MainImage1.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="Our philosophy at Six Physio is ‘two heads are better than one’. The teamwork between specialist rehab and manual therapist is seamless. We will get to the cause of the problem and show you dynamic, tried and tested rehab strategies. Over 42&#37; of patients who come to us with back pain have failed elsewhere to manage their pain."
        clinicianImage1="SixPhysio/3Brad.JPG"
        clinicianName1="Brad Jones - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Six Physio (Harley Street)" 
        lat="51.5170690" 
        lng="-0.1458440" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="Six Physio Harley Street"
        address2="2 Harley Street" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="W1G 9PA" 
        country="UK"
        phone="020 7636 6353"
        email="Harley@sixphysio.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.sixphysio.com" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="physiotherapy" 
        practiceImage="SixPhysio/MainImage1.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="Our philosophy at Six Physio is ‘two heads are better than one’. The teamwork between specialist rehab and manual therapist is seamless. We will get to the cause of the problem and show you dynamic, tried and tested rehab strategies. Over 42&#37; of patients who come to us with back pain have failed elsewhere to manage their pain."
        clinicianImage1="SixPhysio/4MattTodman.JPG"
        clinicianName1="Matt Todman - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1="Matt Todman makes no bones about his Essex boy status. After being politely asked to leave school at the age of 16, Matt had the choice to either train to become a chef or try to gain some further education. The education battle was won and after he learnt how to spell Physiotherapy, gained a place at the Middlesex hospital, London qualifying in 1992. The next 2 years in the NHS were spent making all his patients worse, and the simple discovery that if you make them worse, then do the opposite of what was taught and make them better. An 18-month period overseas, sitting on beaches whetted his appetite to officially learn more and try to gain an MSc at UCL. Funnily enough he was initially rejected for being too flippant in the interview. It was then almost impossible not to be accepted! Finally completing his MSc in 1998 and after lots of undercover work the suggestion that Matt might be really good at this physio lark was now becoming a reality. Working with Mark and teaching the McConnell concept to the UK developed, honed and focussed Matt`s skills, talent and good looks. He is now often referred to by the Chartered Society of Physiotherapy to give his expert opinion on TV, radio and to the newspapers. He continues to guest lecture at different MSc courses around the UK, because he truly believes that poor physio is not on. Matt recognises, and is recognised by his cohorts for, the importance of a simple approach to often-complex musculoskeletal problems. He does so without losing any of his clinical excellence to get the very best result for every patient and from every physiotherapist in his team. You`ll find him at the weekend either pegging it along the Thames path; trying to find the next Banksy or waxing his Ford Escort, who says you can`t take the boy out of Essex!"
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Six Physio (Kensington)" 
        lat="51.5015230" 
        lng="-0.1894630" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="15 Young Street"
        address2="" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="W8 5EH" 
        country="UK"
        phone="020 7937 8877"
        email="Kensington@sixphysio.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.sixphysio.com" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="physiotherapy" 
        practiceImage="SixPhysio/MainImage1.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="Our philosophy at Six Physio is ‘two heads are better than one’. The teamwork between specialist rehab and manual therapist is seamless. We will get to the cause of the problem and show you dynamic, tried and tested rehab strategies. Over 42&#37; of patients who come to us with back pain have failed elsewhere to manage their pain."
        clinicianImage1="SixPhysio/5Tim.JPG"
        clinicianName1="Tim Galliver - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Six Physio (Leadenhall)" 
        lat="51.5137860" 
        lng="-0.0805550" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="106 Leadenhall Street"
        address2="" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="EC3A 4AA" 
        country="UK"
        phone="020 7929 4007"
        email="Leadenhall@sixphysio.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.sixphysio.com" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="physiotherapy" 
        practiceImage="SixPhysio/MainImage1.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="Our philosophy at Six Physio is ‘two heads are better than one’. The teamwork between specialist rehab and manual therapist is seamless. We will get to the cause of the problem and show you dynamic, tried and tested rehab strategies. Over 42&#37; of patients who come to us with back pain have failed elsewhere to manage their pain."
        clinicianImage1="SixPhysio/6Kelly.JPG"
        clinicianName1="Kelly Robinson - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Six Physio (Monument)" 
        lat="51.5105480" 
        lng="-0.0855780" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="4th Floor"
        address2="2A Eastcheap" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="EC3M 1AA" 
        country="UK"
        phone="020 3206 1082"
        email="monument@sixphysio.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.sixphysio.com" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="physiotherapy" 
        practiceImage="SixPhysio/MainImage1.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="Our philosophy at Six Physio is ‘two heads are better than one’. The teamwork between specialist rehab and manual therapist is seamless. We will get to the cause of the problem and show you dynamic, tried and tested rehab strategies. Over 42&#37; of patients who come to us with back pain have failed elsewhere to manage their pain."
        clinicianImage1="SixPhysio/7James.jpg"
        clinicianName1="James Thompson - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2="SixPhysio/8Jennifer.JPG"
        clinicianName2="Jennifer Hird - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Six Physio (Moorgate)" 
        lat="51.5170860" 
        lng="-0.0883890" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="43 London Wall"
        address2="" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="EC2M 5TF" 
        country="UK"
        phone="020 7374 2244"
        email="Moorgate@sixphysio.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.sixphysio.com" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="physiotherapy" 
        practiceImage="SixPhysio/MainImage1.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="Our philosophy at Six Physio is ‘two heads are better than one’. The teamwork between specialist rehab and manual therapist is seamless. We will get to the cause of the problem and show you dynamic, tried and tested rehab strategies. Over 42&#37; of patients who come to us with back pain have failed elsewhere to manage their pain."
        clinicianImage1="SixPhysio/9AlexHunter.jpg"
        clinicianName1="Alex Hunter - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Six Physio (Parsons Green)" 
        lat="51.4772640" 
        lng="-0.2013220" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="699 Fulham Road"
        address2="" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="SW6 5UJ" 
        country="UK"
        phone="020 7371 7666"
        email="" 
        details=""
        web="www.sixphysio.com" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="physiotherapy" 
        practiceImage="SixPhysio/MainImage1.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="Our philosophy at Six Physio is ‘two heads are better than one’. The teamwork between specialist rehab and manual therapist is seamless. We will get to the cause of the problem and show you dynamic, tried and tested rehab strategies. Over 42&#37; of patients who come to us with back pain have failed elsewhere to manage their pain."
        clinicianImage1="SixPhysio/10Gary.JPG"
        clinicianName1="Gary Jones - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2="SixPhysio/MainImage2.jpg"
        clinicianName2="Atty Roberts - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Spine Plus Clinics" 
        lat="51.6108460" 
        lng="0.0902160" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="2a Oak Lodge Ave"
        address2="" 
        city="Chigwell" 
        state="Essex" 
        postal="IG7 5HZ" 
        country="UK"
        phone="0845 649 2979"
        email="info@spineplus.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
clinical pilates (one to one),
electro-acupuncture,
ergonomics,
interferential and therapeutic ultrasound,
knee clinic,
low back pain,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
neck pain,
osteopathy,
personal training,
physiotherapy,
post surgery physiotherapy,
postural correction,
remedial massage,
sports massage,
whiplash" 
        practiceImage="SpinePlusClinics/MainImage1.png" 
        practiceDescription="Multidisciplinary clinics in London dedicated to expert spinal therapy managed by a team of physiotherapists and osteopaths."
        clinicianImage1=""
        clinicianName1=""
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Sports and Spinal Physio LTD" 
        lat="51.6374520" 
        lng="0.3560290" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="24 Tallon Road"
        address2="Hutton" 
        city="Brentwood" 
        state="Essex" 
        postal="CM13 1TE" 
        country="UK"
        phone="+441277219553"
        email="dan@sportsandspinalphysio.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="http://www.sportsandspinalphysio.co.uk" 
        hours1="8am-9pm mon-fri" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
chronic pain management,
clinical pilates (one to one),
ergonomics,
gait analysis,
gym,
home visits,
interferential and therapeutic ultrasound,
knee clinic,
low back pain,
musculo-skeletal services,
musculoskeletal ultrasound,
neck pain,
nutritional therapy,
physiotherapy,
pilates,
podiatry,
postural correction,
rehabilitation services,
remedial massage,
running clinic,
sports massage,
sports medicine,
vestibular physiotherapy,
whiplash" 
        practiceImage="SportsandSpinalPhysioLTD/MainImage1.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="Sports and Spinal Physio is a private clinic based in Mortons Personal Fitness Club. Are specialist interests are back, neck and sports related pain and injury. Our services include IDD Spinal Decompression therapy, Motor Control Rehabilitation, Clinical Pilates, Headache and Migraine Management, Video Gait Analysis Physiotherapy, Podiatry and Sports Massage."
        clinicianImage1="SportsandSpinalPhysioLTD/MainImage2.jpg"
        clinicianName1="Sports and Spinal Physio LTD"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Sprint Physiotherapy" 
        lat="51.5025170" 
        lng="-0.1939830" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="2 Drayson Mews"
        address2="Kensington" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="W8 4LY" 
        country="UK"
        phone="020 7938 1350"
        email="info@sprintphysio.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="www.sprintphysio.co.uk" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="clinical pilates (one to one),
exercise classes,
nutritional therapy,
remedial massage" 
        practiceImage="SprintPhysiotherapy/MainImage1.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="At Sprint Physiotherapy we have a unique approach to each and every individual. It’s not simply treatment; it’s a process to help you inhabit your body more comfortably, whether that be getting through your working day without pain, recovering from surgery or returning to sport or other hobbies. Our highly experienced team of physiotherapists use a combination of manual therapy and rehabilitation exercises (including Clinical Pilates in our fully equipped gym) to relieve your pain and prevent further injuries. Our friendly clinic offers a warm welcome and the highest standards of care. There is a simple reason why most of our patients are recommended by doctors or friends and family – we are committed to helping you get better."
        clinicianImage1="SprintPhysiotherapy/1camilla.jpg"
        clinicianName1="Camilla Curtis MSc Manipulative Physiotherapy, MMACP, MCSP, SRP - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1="Camilla studied at University College London and the Middlesex Hospital, achieving her Masters in Neuromusculoskeletal Physiotherapy in 1995. Over 20 years her analytical, evidence based approach to assessment and treatment, integrating manual and rehabilitation based strategies has achieved exceptional results for her patients. Her rehabilitation approach is based on a deep understanding of the influence of posture on dynamic activities; gym and clinical Pilates exercises are therefore a key component of the way she drives improvements. Recognising her excellence, Kings College University engages her to act as a clinical tutor and examiner for Masters Students."
        clinicianImage2="SprintPhysiotherapy/2sarah.jpg"
        clinicianName2="Sarah McNaughton BSc Physiotherapy, MCSP, SRP - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio2="Sarah graduated from the University of Cape Town in 2004, and has worked in private practice in South Africa and the UK. She completed her Masters in Sports Physiotherapy at King's College London in September 2010. Sarah has a keen interest in spinal rehabilitation, and is a qualified Clinical Pilates instructor; she also assists in training physiotherapists to teach Pilates. Sarah believes in an integrated, evidence-based approach to physiotherapy treatment, and incorporates Pilates into her treatment sessions where appropriate. She also has an interest in hypermobility and has worked extensively with dancers at the English National Ballet school."
        clinicianImage3="SprintPhysiotherapy/3SophieCook.jpg"
        clinicianName3="Sophie Cook BSc Physiotherapy, MCSP, SRP - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio3="Sophie graduated from Curtin University in Perth, Western Australia with a Bachelor of Physiotherapy. Since graduating, Sophie has worked in private practice, specialising in musculoskeletal, spinal and sports injuries as well as clinical Pilates. She has also worked with elite level athletes and sports people. She holds a postgraduate qualification in clinical Pilates from Dance Medicine Australia and uses it extensively as an effective adjunct to manual treatment. Sophie has both a holistic and analytical approach to understanding and treating the client's presenting problem. She will always aim to identify the underlying causal factors and, with strong manual skills and a personalised approach to rehabilitation and clinical Pilates, she aims to prevent further injury."
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Surrey Physio" 
        lat="51.4068117" 
        lng="-0.1639932" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="409-411 London Road"
        address2="" 
        city="Mitcham" 
        state="Surrey" 
        postal="CR4 4BG" 
        country="UK"
        phone="0208 685 6930"
        email="info@surreyphysio.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="http://www.surreyphysio.co.uk" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
chronic pain management,
clinical pilates (one to one),
ergonomics,
gait analysis,
home visits,
injection therapy,
knee clinic,
low back pain,
musculoskeletal diagnostic ultrasound,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
musculo-skeletal services,
musculoskeletal ultrasound,
neck pain,
neurophysiotherapy,
osteopathy,
osteoporosis physiotherapy,
physiotherapy,
pilates,
podiatry,
post natal physio,
post surgery physiotherapy,
postural correction,
rehabilitation services,
remedial massage,
sports massage,
sports medicine,
whiplash,
women's health,
womens health physiotherapy" 
        practiceImage="SurreyPhysio/MainImage1.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="Surrey Physio is the leading physiotherapy clinic in Surrey, with a reputation of attracting clients from far. The team of highly trained physiotherapists work with a number of top International tennis players, and other athletes, as well as treating members of the public. The clinic has good links with local GP's and Consultants and all insurances are accepted."
        clinicianImage1=""
        clinicianName1=""
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="The Harley Street Spine Clinic" 
        lat="51.5228590" 
        lng="-0.1485080" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="144 Harley Street"
        address2="Marylebone" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="W1G 7LD" 
        country="UK"
        phone="0203 369 8747"
        email="web@harleystreetspineclinic.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.harleystreetspineclinic.com" 
        hours1="Mon - Fri 9am - 8pm" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
clinical pilates (one to one),
ergonomics,
interferential and therapeutic ultrasound,
low back pain,
musculoskeletal ultrasound,
osteopathy,
physiotherapy,
remedial massage,
sports massage,
whiplash" 
        practiceImage="TheHarleyStreetSpineClinic/MainImage.JPG" 
        practiceDescription="A 21st Century Physical Therapy clinic specialising in back and neck pain disorders adopting a modern orthopaedic approach utilises analysis and understanding of the latest diagnostic scans such as MRI, SPECT ST, EOS and others. Treatment provided on-site includes osteopathy, shockwave therapy, dry needling (Medical Acupuncture), one to one clinical Pilates and IDD Computerised Spinal Decompression Therapy which has received notoriety in the USA and has recently been introduced to the UK."
        clinicianImage1="TheHarleyStreetSpineClinic/MainImage1.JPG"
        clinicianName1="The Harley Street Spine Clinic"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="The Partnership Centre For Health and Injury Treatment" 
        lat="51.1511070" 
        lng="0.8854500" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="10 Highpoint Business Village"
        address2="Henwood" 
        city="Ashford" 
        state="Kent" 
        postal="TN24 8DH" 
        country="UK"
        phone="01233 611776"
        email="thepartnershipcentre@googlemail.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.thepartnershipcentre.co.uk" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="physiotherapy" 
        practiceImage="ThePartnershipCentreForHealthandInjuryTreatment/MainImage1.png" 
        practiceDescription="The Partnership is a unique centre of excellence combining physiotherapy, pilates, podiatry and massage therapy. All disciplines complement each other and work towards the same goal of restoring and maintaining natural pain free movement. Our field of speciality is the return of the individual to levels of activity that may be possible following trauma, surgery or physical injury; from simple sprains to complex muscle imbalance problems in the sporting and non-sporting environments. We believe we extend our capacity to supply the highest levels of treatment and care to all of our clients, whether they are elite athletes or not."
        clinicianImage1="ThePartnershipCentreForHealthandInjuryTreatment/1PaulMassey.jpg"
        clinicianName1="Paul Massey - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Third Space Medicine" 
        lat="51.5109930" 
        lng="-0.1359200" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="13 Sherwood Street"
        address2="Soho" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="W1F 7BR" 
        country="UK"
        phone="020 7439 7332"
        email="medical.enquiries@thethirdspace.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.thethirdspace.com" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="hydrotherapy,
injection therapy,
physiotherapy,
pilates" 
        practiceImage="ThirdSpaceMedicine/MainImage1.png" 
        practiceDescription="The Third Space comprises of a fitness facility, pilates studio and an integrated medical centre. Third Space Medicine offers a choice of more than twenty orthodox, complementary, and musculoskeletal therapies delivered by our team of over 20 professional practitioners. Due to the breadth of therapies provided, and the depth of the practitioners’ understanding, we hope that few diseases be they acute or chronic, mental, physical or emotional, organic or structural, will be beyond our ability to help. We can offering short-term rehabilitation packages utilising the fitness facility including pool."
        clinicianImage1="ThirdSpaceMedicine/1BarryWalsh.JPG"
        clinicianName1="Barry Walsh - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1="Specialising in: physiotherapy, pilates, remedial massage, womens health physiotherapy, Spinal manipulation and rehabilitation. Sporting injuries with an interest in biomechanics, uses Pilates reformers too as part of his treatment as appropriate. Email: medical.enquiries@thethirdspace.com"
        clinicianImage2="ThirdSpaceMedicine/2Claire_Lawrence.JPG"
        clinicianName2="Claire Lawrence - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio2="Sports, acute injury, orthopaedics particularly interested in shoulders &amp; knees. Email: medical.enquiries@thethirdspace.com"
        clinicianImage3="ThirdSpaceMedicine/3KevinLidlow.JPG"
        clinicianName3="Kevin Lidlow - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio3="Sports medicine, spinal &amp; peripheral musculoskeletal injuries, Diploma in Orthopaedic Medicine with extended scope licence for injection therapy. Email: medical.enquiries@thethirdspace.com"
        clinicianImage4="ThirdSpaceMedicine/4MarkThomas.JPG"
        clinicianName4="Mark Thomas - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio4="Sports injuries, back pain and all musculo-skeletal problems, licence for Kenalog &amp; Intratraumeel injections. Email: medical.enquiries@thethirdspace.com"
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Trevor Blount Pilates" 
        lat="51.4939700" 
        lng="-0.1751710" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="5 Harrington Road"
        address2="Kensington" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="SW7 3ES" 
        country="UK"
        phone="02075840680"
        email="trevor@trevorblountpilates.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.trevorBlountPilates.com" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="physiotherapy,
pilates" 
        practiceImage="TrevorBlountPilates/MainImage1.bmp" 
        practiceDescription="High Quality Pilates Trevor Blount has been at the forefront of developing modern Pilates for more that 25 years. What makes him and his team exceptional – and different from other Pilates teachers – is their complete understanding of how to use Pilates in a way that is sympathetic to each individual’s anatomical structure. This comes from Trevor’s own daily practise, combined with his experience of teaching a huge range of people with widely different needs. Remedial and Rehabilitation Structural Pilates is Trevor Blount’s description of the way he and his team have, for 25 years, been adapting Pilates and specialising in helping people in the rehabilitation and management of back, postural and functional conditions."
        clinicianImage1="TrevorBlountPilates/1ALEX.jpg"
        clinicianName1="Alex Rose - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1="Specialising in: pilates"
        clinicianImage2="TrevorBlountPilates/2kathryn.jpg"
        clinicianName2="Kathryn Hammersley - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio2="Specialising in: pilates"
        clinicianImage3="TrevorBlountPilates/3TREVOR.jpg"
        clinicianName3="Trevor Blount - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio3="Specialising in: pilates"
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Up and Running" 
        lat="25.1483290" 
        lng="55.2112320" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="Integrated Sports Medical Center"
        address2="969 Al Wasl Road" 
        city="" 
        state="" 
        postal="" 
        country="Dubai"
        phone="+971 4 3284600"
        email="info@upandrunningdubai.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.upandrunningdubai.com" 
        hours1="0700 - 2000 Sunday - Wednesday" 
        hours2="0700 - 1800 Thursday - CLOSED FRIDAY" 
        hours3="0830 - 1700 Saturday" 
        featured="" 
        features="physiotherapy" 
        practiceImage="UpandRunning/logo1.png" 
        practiceDescription="Sports medicine is an interdisciplinary sub-specialty of medicine dealing with the treatment and preventative care of athletes. We focus on recovery from musculoskeletal injuries by restoring function and alleviating pain. Whether your injury is minor or chronic and affects your mobility or enjoyment, we will develop a treatment program specific to your needs and goals."
        clinicianImage1="UpandRunning/JacEley1.jpg"
        clinicianName1="Jaqueline Eley - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1="Jacqueline Eley has had 15 years experience working as a Physiotherapist, after graduating with first class honors from the University of Melbourne in 1994. Jac has extensive experience working as a Physiotherapist in both private and public sectors in Australia, England and Singapore before joining UPANDRUNNING at its inception in 2010."
        clinicianImage2="UpandRunning/LauraBarret2.jpg"
        clinicianName2="Laura Barrett - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio2="Specialising in physiotherapy, Laura graduated from Kings College London with First Class Honours in Physiotherapy in 2004 having gained a degree in human biology at the same institution in 2001. This degree provided her with a solid and in depth understanding of all areas of physiotherapy."
        clinicianImage3="UpandRunning/LeeJohnson3.jpg"
        clinicianName3="Lee Johnson - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio3="Lee graduated with First Class Honours in Sports &amp; Rehabilitation Prevention and has been involved in sport for most of his life. He enjoys helping sports participants get back on the road to recovery. He offers a holistic approach enabling the whole treatment plan to be also encompassed by the professionals he works with. The aim is to get the sports participant back to their chosen sport as soon as possible, and to get them performing at a higher level than before their injury."
        clinicianImage4="UpandRunning/SharonParsons4.jpg"
        clinicianName4="Sharon Parsons - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio4="Clinical and Diagnostic skills achieved in over 20 years of physical therapy practice. Sharon's exposure and access to world class Surgeons, sports medicine arenas and her own continued education has ensured a high level of skill and knowledge in all areas relating to rehabilitation, biomechanics and physical dysfunction."
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Waterside Physiotherapy" 
        lat="51.5011410" 
        lng="-0.0213910" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="One Parker House, Waterside"
        address2="Admirals Way" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="E14 9UQ" 
        country="UK"
        phone="020 7987 8899"
        email="info@watersidephysiotherapy.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="www.watersidephysiotherapy.co.uk" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
interferential and therapeutic ultrasound,
musculoskeletal, diagnostic, ultrasound,
physiotherapy" 
        practiceImage="WatersidePhysiotherapy/WSLogo.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="Think... experts in sports injuries, rehabilitation, back care and ultrasound imaging. It sounds simple - but that's what we're good at! We've been doing it for over 15 years in Canary Wharf and we see most patients through personal recommendation or referral by leading specialists."
        clinicianImage1="WatersidePhysiotherapy/EmmaWeaver1.jpg"
        clinicianName1="Emma Weaver - BSc(Hons) Musculoskeletal Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1="Emma graduated in 2005 with an Honours degree from the University of the West of England and then completed 2 years in the NHS focusing on musculoskeletal physiotherapy. She then moved to New Zealand working in private practice for a Sports Injury Clinic &amp; Medical Centre.
During this time she worked with elite athletes including tri-athletes, tennis players and the All Blacks rugby team at international level. She also worked with the New Zealand Ice Hockey Team and with international golfers at the PGA New Zealand Open. Emma assisted with setting up the Adidas Soccer Academy for youth players, promoting injury prevention and body awareness for children starting their sporting careers."
        clinicianImage2="WatersidePhysiotherapy/RobertLaus3.jpg"
        clinicianName2="Robert Laus - BSc HPC MCSP Clinical Director"
        clinicianBio2="Robert has over 21 years experience as a physiotherapist. After completing his degree course in 1989 in the Netherlands, Robert became a senior partner in Private Practice. Robert specialises in Diagnostic Musculoskeletal Ultrasound Imaging within Sports and Orthopaedic Medicine. As one of the first in the UK, he fully integrated it within his physiotherapy clinics 12 years ago and is one of the most experienced physiotherapists using ultrasound imaging within sports and orthopaedic rehabilitation in Europe."
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="West 1 Physiotherapy" 
        lat="51.5213990" 
        lng="-0.1478060" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="106 Harley street"
        address2="Marylebone" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="W1G 7JE" 
        country="UK"
        phone="020 7935 5652"
        email="info@west1physio.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.west1physio.com" 
        hours1="Clinic Opening Hours: Monday - Friday 8am - 7pm" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
chronic pain management,
clinical pilates (one to one),
ergonomics,
interferential and therapeutic ultrasound,
knee clinic,
low back pain,
musculoskeletal diagnostic ultrasound,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
musculo-skeletal services,
musculoskeletal ultrasound,
neck pain,
neurophysiotherapy,
physiotherapy,
pilates,
podiatry,
post natal physio,
post surgery physiotherapy,
postural correction,
rehabilitation services,
remedial massage,
sports massage" 
        practiceImage="West1Physiotherapy/mainImage1.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="West 1 Physiotherapy &amp; Pilates is a well established clinic in the medical heart of central London, Harley Street.
We combine a professional and holistic approach to establish the underlying cause of your pain. Our highly experienced physiotherapists provide accurate assessment and clinical diagnosis to provide effective treatment for a broad spectrum of disorders. This ranges from work related problems to sports injuries and post surgical rehabilitation."
        clinicianImage1=""
        clinicianName1=""
        clinicianBio1=""
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="West End Physiotherapy" 
        lat="51.5154250" 
        lng="-0.1357790" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="191 Wardour street"
        address2="Soho" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="W1F 8ZE" 
        country="UK"
        phone="02077346263"
        email="Info@wephysio.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="www.wephysio.co.uk" 
        hours1="8am-8pm Monday to Friday." 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
chronic pain management,
clinical pilates (one to one),
ergonomics,
gait analysis,
home visits,
hypermobility,
interferential and therapeutic ultrasound,
knee clinic,
low back pain,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
musculo-skeletal services,
musculoskeletal ultrasound,
neck pain,
neurophysiotherapy,
osteopathy,
osteoporosis physiotherapy,
physiotherapy,
podiatry,
post surgery physiotherapy,
postural correction,
rehabilitation services,
remedial massage,
sports massage,
vestibular physiotherapy,
whiplash" 
        practiceImage="WestEndPhysiotherapy/headerwhite1.png" 
        practiceDescription="We pride ourselves on staying at the cutting edge of medical research. As such we regularly up skill our team so they can include the latest medical advancements in the treatments given to their patients. Our physiotherapists are skilled at spinal mobilisation and manipulation, post operative recovery, acupuncture and muscle imbalance retraining."
        clinicianImage1="WestEndPhysiotherapy/AlexLong.jpg"
        clinicianName1="Alex Long - BHSc.(Physio.), PGd. (Manual Therapy), MCSP, HPC reg."
        clinicianBio1="After graduating in Lyon (France) , Alex had the opportunity to work in Tignes and La Plagne Ski resorts for over 8 years, during which he gained great experience in the field of acute sport injuries and return to physical activities by working with skiing teams on a daily basis. In 2007, an opportunity to move permanently to London arised and he continued to work with athletes as well as office workers and the postural issues they encounter. Being the M.D of our clinic, Alex is now mainly involved in the running of our clinic, but still available to treat old patients. When not working, Alex takes his 2 young daughters skiing and keeps fit by running, cycling and regularly takes part in half marathons to help raise money for the Parkinson Society."
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2=""
        clinicianBio2=""
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="West London Physio" 
        lat="51.4995200" 
        lng="-0.1887410" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="23 Ansdell Street"
        address2="" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="W8 5BN" 
        country="UK"
        phone="0207 937 1628"
        email="info@westlondonphysio.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="www.westlondonphysio.co.uk" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="physiotherapy,
sports massage" 
        practiceImage="WestLondonPhysio/MainImage1.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="We’re not a chain, we run on time, we listen and we try to understand. We establish your expectations.  We assess you, establish the diagnosis and find your pain – that is really important. Then we explain the problem and how we are going to fix it, in a way that we know works, and that you are also happy with – it’s simple but that’s why it works so well. West London Physiotherapy is a people oriented business, recognising that most patients come via personal recommendation or from your GP or surgeon. Our reputation is built on good outcomes so that means we are results focussed, going to great lengths to ensure you are happy with our service."
        clinicianImage1="WestLondonPhysio/cameron.jpg"
        clinicianName1="Cameron Tudor - Clinical Director and Prescriber"
        clinicianBio1="The founder and Director of West London Physiotherapy, Cameron has two decades of experience as a physiotherapist in Australia and the UK. His experience and passion for assisting people to regain strength and recover from injuries led to the foundation of West London Physiotherapy in 2007. Cameron’s unique philosophy forms the basis of treatment at West London Physiotherapy – a combination of listening to understand the patients’ needs and the affect that pain is having in their lives, then establishing goals and working together to achieve them."
        clinicianImage2="WestLondonPhysio/kamSnowman.jpg"
        clinicianName2="Kam Sowman - Musculoskeletal and Sports Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio2="Kam’s areas of speciality include back and neck pain, sports and running injuries, and long term injury associated with sedentary life styles. He has a passion for human movement and biomechanics in both ergonomic, work and sports settings. He has extensive post graduate experience in this field and uses a combination of manual therapy, postural/movement correction, and specific exercise prescription to get to the root of the problem and devise a successful treatment. He also holds post graduate qualifications in dry needling, acupuncture, and spinal manipulation."
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Westminster Physiotherapy and Pilates Centre" 
        lat="51.4981120" 
        lng="-0.1450160" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="9 Lower Grosvenor Place"
        address2="" 
        city="London" 
        state="" 
        postal="SW1W 0EN" 
        country="UK"
        phone="0207 834 3700"
        email="reception@westminsterphysio.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="www.westminsterphysio.co.uk" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="chronic pain management,
clinical pilates (one to one),
exercise classes,
musculo-skeletal physiotherapy,
post surgery physiotherapy" 
       practiceImage="WestminsterPhysiotherapyandPilatesCentre/WestminsterMain.png" 
        practiceDescription="The Westminster Physiotherapy and Pilates Centre (WPPC) is a well respected, highly professional practice , established in 1993. It is our passion to help our clients with musculoskeletal conditions achieve their goals with the most appropriate treatment, be that physiotherapy, Pilates rehabilitation, massage therapy, nutritional advice and personal training. We aim to resolve the presenting condition and permanently prevent re-occurrence. We have close and longstanding working relationships with many of London’s top specialist Consultants."
        clinicianImage1="WestminsterPhysiotherapyandPilatesCentre/CY1.jpg"
        clinicianName1="Claire Yuill - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1="Claire is a Chartered Physiotherapist who treats patients at our Victoria centre. She has extensive experience in treating musculo-skeletal conditions in the whole body but has a special interest in the management of knee pain and post knee surgery. She has worked closely with Knee Specialist Consultants in London for several years."
        clinicianImage2="WestminsterPhysiotherapyandPilatesCentre/CF2.jpg"
        clinicianName2="Clare Fone WPPC Founder - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio2="Clare founded WPPC in 1994 and is a Chartered Physiotherapist who treats patients, and runs a number of exercise classes, at all WPPC’s locations. Clare specialises in pain management and all spinal and peripheral joint conditions, including sports injuries."
        clinicianImage3="WestminsterPhysiotherapyandPilatesCentre/DP3.jpg"
        clinicianName3="Daniela Philipp - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio3="Daniela is a Chartered Physiotherapist who treats patients at our Victoria centre. She uses a functional and holistic approach to therapy. She is very interested in finding the underlying cause of each problem, then treating and instructing her patients to prevent further occurrence and thus aiming for lasting results."
        clinicianImage4="WestminsterPhysiotherapyandPilatesCentre/IM4.jpg"
        clinicianName4="Inge Marsden - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio4="Inge is a Chartered Physiotherapist at the Victoria practice having recently joined Westminster Physiotherapy as our Clinical Lead. She became a physiotherapist whilst working at the Royal Free Hospital, London in 1999. She specialised in Musculoskeletal conditions in 2002 and has been working in this area ever since."
        clinicianImage5="WestminsterPhysiotherapyandPilatesCentre/5.jpg"
        clinicianName5="Ria Komodromos - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio5="Ria is a Chartered Physiotherapist who carries out rehabilitation sessions at our Victoria and Mayfair locations. Her speciality is rehabilitation for the prevention of injury, as well as following injury. She completed a degree in Sports Science at Loughborough University in 2008 and then went on to complete a Masters in Physiotherapy."
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Witty Pask and Buckingham" 
        lat="52.2382510" 
        lng="-0.8777250" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="56 Billing Road"
        address2="" 
        city="Northampton" 
        state="Northamptonshire" 
        postal="NN1 5DB" 
        country="UK"
        phone="01604 601641"
        email="reception@wpbphysio.co.uk" 
        details=""
        web="www.wpbphysio.co.uk" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
hydrotherapy,
physiotherapy,
pilates" 
        practiceImage="WittyPaskandBuckingham/WPBlogio.bmp" 
        practiceDescription="30 years of treating musculoskeletal sports and orthopaedic injury. 18 years of England Rugby Senior Squad, British and Irish Lions, British Athletics, 3 Olympic Games. 30 Years of association with Northampton Saints Rugby. Specialists in spinal rehabilitation with combination of Physiotherapy, Pilates and Rehabilitation form back ground with Headley Court Services Rehab Centre. Association with spinal surgeons like Nick Birch where Chris Heywood acts as Research Assistance and right hand man. Specialist Clinical Pilates with Leian Lee combines to make spinal rehabilitation one of our particular skills alongside Sports Injury. Combined Clinic with Professor Bill Ribbans and Mr David Stock enhances our orthopaedic service with Consultant opinion, musculoskeletal imaging and therapies."
        clinicianImage1="WittyPaskandBuckingham/BillMacKay.jpg"
        clinicianName1="Bill MacKay MSc, MCSP- Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1="Bill trained in the Royal Air Force and graduated as a physiotherapist in 1969. He has served extensively at home and abroad in a variety of disciplines, including orthopaedics, intensive rehabilitation and sports injury management. He has been physiotherapist to the Singapore State XV, the England Rugby XV and a touring Wallabies side. He has also looked after a number of semi-professional soccer teams over the years and is currently a lecturer for the FA on sports injuries."
        clinicianImage2="WittyPaskandBuckingham/ChrisHeywood.jpg"
        clinicianName2="Chris Heywood MSc, BSc, MCSP - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio2="Chris qualified as a physiotherapist in 2000 and has worked extensively in the private environment since 2004. He practices his physiotherapy at the renowned ‘Witty, Pask and Buckingham’ Clinic, based in Northampton, and is a specialist spinal practitioner concentrating on the lower back."
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3=""
        clinicianBio3=""
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4=""
        clinicianBio4=""
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5=""
        clinicianBio5=""
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
        
        <marker 
        name="Wye Physiotherapy Clinic Ltd" 
        lat="51.1827070" 
        lng="0.9434910" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address="71 Scotton Street"
        address2="Wye" 
        city="Ashford" 
        state="Kent" 
        postal="TN25 5BW" 
        country="UK"
        phone="01233 812596"
        email="jowyephysio@yahoo.com" 
        details=""
        web="www.wyephysiotherapyclinic.co.uk" 
        hours1="Monday - Friday 8AM - 7PM Saturday 9AM -1PM" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="acupuncture,
chronic pain management,
clinical pilates (one to one),
hypermobility" 
        practiceImage="WyePhysiotherapyClinic.jpg" 
        practiceDescription="The team has a strong belief in manual therapy and utilise a mixture of manual and soft tissue techniques, alongside an exercise programme designed to aid the patient to a speedy recovery and self management. At Wye Physiotherapy Clinic we also offer Acupuncture and Pilates sessions . Domiciliary visits are also available."
        clinicianImage1=""
        clinicianName1="Janice Sencer - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio1="Specialising in chronic pain management, ergonomics, home visits, hypermobility, interferential and therapeutic ultrasound, musculo-skeletal physiotherapy, musculo-skeletal services, physiotherapy, post surgery physiotherapy, postural correction, rehabilitation services, whiplash. Email: jowyephysio@yahoo.com"
        clinicianImage2=""
        clinicianName2="Jo Bond - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio2="Specialising in low back pain, musculo-skeletal physiotherapy, musculo-skeletal services, neck pain, physiotherapy, post surgery physiotherapy, postural correction, rehabilitation services, sports medicine, whiplash. Email: jowyephysio@yahoo.com"
        clinicianImage3=""
        clinicianName3="Jo Bridgland - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio3="Specialising in: 
acupuncture, chronic pain management, ergonomics, hydrotherapy, hypermobility, interferential and therapeutic ultrasound, low back pain, musculo-skeletal physiotherapy, musculo-skeletal services, neck pain, physiotherapy, postural correction, rehabilitation services, whiplash. Email: jowyephysio@yahoo.com"
        clinicianImage4=""
        clinicianName4="Keighley Hawkins - Support Staff"
        clinicianBio4="Specialising in clinical pilates (one to one), pilates, yoga. Email: jowyephysio@yahoo.com"
        clinicianImage5=""
        clinicianName5="Nuno Teixeira - Physiotherapist"
        clinicianBio5="Specialising in chronic pain management, ergonomics, hypermobility, low back pain, musculo-skeletal physiotherapy, musculo-skeletal services, neck pain, physiotherapy, post surgery physiotherapy, postural correction, rehabilitation services, whiplash. Email: jowyephysio@yahoo.com"
        clinicianImage6=""
        clinicianName6=""
        clinicianBio6=""
        clinicianImage7=""
        clinicianName7=""
        clinicianBio7=""
        clinicianImage8=""
        clinicianName8=""
        clinicianBio8=""/>
<!--
        <marker 
        name="" 
        lat="" 
        lng="" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address=""
        address2="" 
        city="" 
        state="" 
        postal="" 
        country="UK"
        phone=""
        email="" 
        details=""
        web="" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="" />
        
        <marker 
        name="" 
        lat="" 
        lng="" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address=""
        address2="" 
        city="" 
        state="" 
        postal="" 
        country="UK"
        phone=""
        email="" 
        details=""
        web="" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="" />
        
        <marker 
        name="" 
        lat="" 
        lng="" 
        category="Physiotherapist" 
        address=""
        address2="" 
        city="" 
        state="" 
        postal="" 
        country="UK"
        phone=""
        email="" 
        details=""
        web="" 
        hours1="" 
        hours2="" 
        hours3="" 
        featured="" 
        features="" />
-->


    </markers>